<?xml version="1.0"?><?mso-application progid="Excel.Sheet"?><Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel" xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40"><DocumentProperties xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"><LastAuthor>Djurre van Dijk</LastAuthor><Created>2019-06-25T15:52:57Z</Created><LastSaved>2019-06-28T21:44:03Z</LastSaved><Version>16.00</Version></DocumentProperties><OfficeDocumentSettings xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"><AllowPNG/></OfficeDocumentSettings><ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"><WindowHeight>9150</WindowHeight><WindowWidth>21570</WindowWidth><WindowTopX>32767</WindowTopX><WindowTopY>32767</WindowTopY><MaxChange>0.0001</MaxChange><ProtectStructure>False</ProtectStructure><ProtectWindows>False</ProtectWindows></ExcelWorkbook><Styles><Style ss:ID="Default" ss:Name="Normal"><Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/><Borders/><Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="11" ss:Color="#000000"/><Interior/><NumberFormat/><Protection/></Style><Style ss:ID="s62"><Alignment ss:Vertical="Top" ss:WrapText="1"/></Style></Styles><Worksheet ss:Name="Script"><Table x:FullColumns="1" x:FullRows="1" ss:StyleID="s62" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15"><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="142.5"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="84.75"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="278.25"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="144.75"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="176.25"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="117.75"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="278.25"/><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SPECIES_EMPIRE</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">The DEV TEAM / MISC NOTES column contains info on what text between { } signs means (if applicable). It usually stands for either a numeric value, or a numeric value with an icon. Text between [ ] signs stands for a certain type of icon. </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="60"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SCENE ID</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TEXT ID</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ENGLISH STRING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCALIZED STRING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ALTERNATIVE ENGLISH STRING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ALTERNATIVE LOCALIZED STRING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCALIZATION NOTES</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DEV TEAM / MISC NOTES</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">RACE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME_SINGULAR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Paragon</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">完人</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_TROOPER</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Soldier</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">士兵</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="409.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_TROOPER</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“The colony is astir with rumors. Paragon soldiers come, demanding tribute. The treasures they take to the Star Hold where the Paragon elite enclaves decide how to divide the remaining spoils of our communities. Thousands are starving. We have no option but to flee to the countryside with only scraps of machinery and armor. How can we riot when even their most basic soldier's ranged weapons cut us down? Their cybernetics keep them in peak conditioning while we starve. Are we destined to return to savagery and wander this world as nomads?”— Cully Day, Civilian, “RV-3504H: Spoken Lore Interpreted”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“殖民地内谣言四起，声称完人的士兵来到这里索要贡品。他们将宝藏带往星辰壁垒，那里也是完人精英决定如何分割我们社区剩余战利品的地方。数以千计的人正在忍受饥饿。我们别无选择，只能带着一些机械和护甲残屑逃到向下去。他们最普通的士兵手中的远程武器都能轻易将我们击倒，我们又如何才能发动暴乱呢？他们的神经机械使他们始终保持全盛状态，而我们却在忍饥挨饿。难道我们命中注定要重回蛮荒，像游牧民族一样穿梭于这个世界吗？”- 库里·戴伊，平民，“RV-3504H：解读的口头传说”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8"><Data ss:Type="String">Edit: "How can we riot against even their most basic soldier whose range weapons cut us down?" -&gt; "How can we riot when even their most basic soldier's ranged weapons cut us down?"</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_GUARD</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Guard</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国守卫</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="315"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_GUARD</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“Listen child. Papa’s grandpapa remembered the Star Union. A time of gods and wealth. I see you eyeing their colony of eerie lights. Beware! Where gods dream, their guards watch. The same guards that watched in the age of abundance. Once their eyes were bright like yours, little one, but now they are dark sockets. If you go there seeking treasure, all you will find is death. Do not tempt the Paragon—the fallen gods—or their servants. We simple scavengers cannot defeat their powers. You cannot kill those already dead.”— Lyra Day, Nomad, “RV-6678H: Spoken Lore Interpreted”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“听着，孩子。爸爸的爷爷经历过星际联盟时代，那是一个众神与财富的年代。我看得出你在看向他们的殖民地时眼神诡异。听好了！众神进入梦乡的地方，一定有守卫把守，他们也曾目睹过那个繁盛的年代。他们的眼睛也曾像你一样明亮，小家伙，但现在他们的眼中只剩下空洞。如果你去那里寻找宝藏，你能找到的只有死亡。不要招惹完人，他们是堕落的神明，也不要招惹他们的仆人。我们只不过是一群拾荒者，无法与他们抗争。你无法杀掉那些已死之人。”- 莱拉·戴伊，游牧民，“RV-6678H：解读的口头传说”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8"><Data ss:Type="String">Edit: added "the" before "fallen"</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_HEAVY_TROOPER</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Heavy Soldier</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">重型士兵</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="240"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_HEAVY_TROOPER</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“If you’re going to infiltrate the Paragon complex, you’ll need keywords to get past the Heavy Soldiers. These ancient walkers are guardians to their colony of dreams. They only heed Technoprophets. If our intelligence is correct, this week’s passwords are in your dataloggers. If the intelligence is not correct, you’ll want to run. Heavy Soldiers are sure-footed and single-minded, so disorienting guild mind-tricks won’t affect them. You’re not outfitted to withstand a blow from their heavy repeater guns or their shoulder demolisher rockets.”— Chemish Abbadon, “RV-6544F: Escapades in Stealth”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“如果你打算渗透完人建筑，你需要先获得通过重型士兵的密码。这些古代的行者是他们梦境殖民地的守护者，只会听从科技先知的命令。如果我们的情报无误，这周的密码就在你的数据日志中。如果情报是错的，你就快跑吧。重型士兵脚步沉稳，意志坚定，一般的迷惑伎俩奈何不了他们。你的装备绝对承受不住他们的重型连发枪和他们肩上的粉碎者火箭弹。”- 切米什·阿巴顿，“RV-6544F：潜入”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8"><Data ss:Type="String">added "affect" in the sentence "guild mind-tricks won’t them"</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PARAGON_FANATIC</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fanatic</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">狂热者</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="270"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PARAGON_FANATIC</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“You call us Fanatics, but the Technoprophets ordained us. We are believers. We preach Paragon immortality. We hope for eternal life and wait for the return of the one true CORE. Long ago, our prophets offered immortality to all the world, but in the end, the unworthy embraced madness and killed themselves. Our purpose sees beyond oblivion’s decay. We overcharge the imperial soul, unlocking potential in others who embrace Paragon technology. Receive each covenant body-mod leading to everlasting life. You too can join our immortal communion.”— Fan Pree Churr, “RV-9947R: Paragon Proselytes”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“你们称呼我们为狂热者，但科技先知曾经任命过我们，我们是信徒。我们为完人的不朽而四处布道，我们希望得到永生并等待真正的核心回归。很久之前，我们的先知给全世界带来了不朽。但最后，那些渣滓却拥抱了疯狂，互相残杀。我们的目标是见证湮灭之后的腐朽，我们强化了帝国的灵魂，为那些接受完人科技的人释放潜能。接受每一个契约身体模块将带来永恒的生命，你们也可以加入我们的不朽交谈。”- 范·普雷·丘尔，“RV-9947R：完人皈依者”</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PARAGON_TECHNO_PROPHET</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Techno Prophet</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">科技先知</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="285"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PARAGON_TECHNO_PROPHET</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“The madman called to me from a hover-pulpit. ‘It’s always been thus!’ He cried out. ‘Prophets lead their fallen people. Here we build a colony of dreams, while the heavens scorch the world with fire. Just a few implants! Your friends are happy now. Join us! Cease wandering this world as one of the fallen.’ I remained hidden, preferring my fallen state to the vacant drooling expressions left upon my traveling companion’s faces after the Technoprophet and his colony of Paragon servants welcomed them into paradise.”— Mah Reg’Nib, “RV-22299X: Forlorn Fantasy Destinations”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“那个疯子在一个悬浮的布道坛上叫住了我：‘一直都是如此！’他大声地喊道，‘先知指引着他们失落的人民。当天堂用火焰炙烤这个世界时，我们却在这里建造充满梦境的殖民地。只需要几个植入物！你的朋友现在很开心。加入我们吧！不要再作为堕落者在这个世间游荡。’但我仍然没有露面。比起那些被科技先知和完人仆从迎入天堂的同游之人满脸空洞留着口水的样子，我更喜欢当一个他们口中所说的堕落者。”- 玛·瑞格尼布，“RV-22299X：凄凉幻想终点”</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_SUBMARINE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Imperial Submarine</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国潜水艇</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="285"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_SUBMARINE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“In an apple barrel, floating in the sea, almost out of apples, I collided with a metal box protruding from the water’s surface. On top was a hatch, so I let myself in. It was an Imperial Revenant Submarine, nearly invisible in the water. Its railgun and behemoth drone were intact but not programmed to blow up apple barrels. The crew had mostly malfunctioned, so the sub was travelling in circles. After executing a few convenient imperial command codes, I convinced them I should be in charge and we navigated to safety.”— Mah Reg’Nib, “RV-22303X: Forlorn Fantasy Destinations”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“我藏在一个苹果桶里在大海上漂浮，但苹果已经所剩不多了。这时，我撞到了水面上一个凸起的金属盒子。盒子的顶端有一个窗口，于是我溜了进去。这是一艘帝国幽魂潜水艇，在水中几乎瞧不见它的身影。它搭载的轨道炮和巨兽无人机虽然未受损伤，但也绝不会向苹果桶开火。船员几乎全部出了故障，所以这艘潜艇才会一直在转圈。在输入了几个简单的帝国命令代码后，我说服了他们让我来指挥。最后，我们平安地回来了。”- 玛·瑞格尼布，“RV-22303X：凄凉幻想终点”</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">INFERNO_SUBMARINE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Imperial Inferno Submarine</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国地狱火潜水艇</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="270"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">INFERNO_SUBMARINE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“I came to the ocean because water extinguishes fire. As a child, Promethean zealots set my parent’s village ablaze. They claimed fire would purify the world. The fires robbed me of all I ever loved. I thought I’d find safety among the waves. Then I saw the reddish glow of an Imperial Revenant Inferno Submarine. With no explanation it surfaced, lobbing inferno shells at every ship. The penetrating flames consumed them all. Fire spread across the surface of the water. There is no escape from the zealot’s fire.”— Captain Vicer Roundy, “RV-4562C: Empires of Ash”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“我选择到海上来，是因为水能灭火。在我还小的时候，圣火狂热者将我父母所在的村庄烧成了灰烬。他们声称火焰能够净化这个世界。那场大火夺走了我深爱的一切。我认为自己身处海浪之中能够获得安全感，直到我看到了帝国地狱火潜水艇中发出的红色光芒。它突然出现，向每一艘船只发射地狱火炮弹。熊熊大火将船只瞬间吞没，火焰甚至扩散到了水面上。面对狂热者的火焰，根本无处可逃”- 维瑟·罗迪队长，“RV-4562C：灰烬帝国”</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">BEHEMOTH_SUBMARINE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Imperial Behemoth Submarine</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国巨兽潜水艇</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="270"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">BEHEMOTH_SUBMARINE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“Once the Star Union fell, the imperial fleet likewise fell into disarray. Here in Harborhome colony we even hear of whole Behemoth Submarines gone rogue. The cyborg crew, once enhanced by their cybernetic implants, are malfunctioning. What remains is some kind of robotic undead thing incapable of distinguishing friend from foe. These huge stealthy submarines once assisted ships with repair nanites. Now, they are just as likely to destroy them with weaponized drones or its railgun. We must find a way to reclaim these naval assets.”— Lars ‘The Admiral’ Robinson, “RV-57688M: Restoring Order to the Sea”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“星际联盟陨落后，帝国舰队似乎也陷入了混乱。在港湾家园殖民地中，我们甚至听说连巨兽潜水艇都叛逃了。那些曾经由神经机械植入物强化过的半机械船员全都发生了故障，变成了一具又一具分不清敌我的行尸走肉。这些巨大的秘密潜艇曾经用修复奈米机器人来协助其他船只，但现在，它们只想用轨道炮和变成了武器的无人机去摧毁一切。我们必须想办法夺回这些海军资产。”- 海军上将拉尔斯·罗宾逊，“RV-57688M：恢复海上的秩序”</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_DRAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Imperial Dragonfly</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国蜻蜓</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="255"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_DRAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“The Technoprophets predicted destruction would hail from the skies. I tried to warn the people but they laughed at me and cast me out of their colony. So the prophet unleashed the Imperial Dragonflies. They poured out a rain of destruction upon the very fools that laughed. From beneath its wings, a spray of angry hornets smote those that raised their weapons. Righteous swarms of fiery darts ripped through their houses, exploding with a concussive roar. Their false temples toppled. Imperial Dragonflies erased their blasphemy. The laughing ceased.”— Fanatic Chul’l Ho, “RV-3390R: Public Notice”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“科技先知预言毁灭将会从天而降。我曾试图警告其他人，但他们却一边嘲笑我，一边将我赶出了他们的殖民地。因此先知释放了帝国蜻蜓，它们给那些嘲笑我的蠢货带去了毁灭。它们翅膀下方可以喷出愤怒的马蜂，给那些胆敢举起武器的人施以重击。正义的蜂群涌入居民的房屋，在呼啸声中爆炸。他们象征虚假的神庙在爆炸中轰然倒塌。帝国蜻蜓抹除了他们的亵渎行径，笑声停止了。”- 狂热者楚尔霍，“RV-3390R：公告”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8"><Data ss:Type="String">Edit: added comma after "wings"</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_DOMINATOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Imperial Walker</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国行者</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="300"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_DOMINATOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“We can’t ignore the mad prophet predicting destruction. He speaks of cryptic doom, but his gods are terrible weapons. He predicts they will lay waste to the colony and only the doleful Imperial Walker shall find home there. I’ve seen what Paragons call an Imperial Walker. It’s a mobile Gatling gun and Arc missile launcher. Who cares if the Paragon claim the Imperial Walker breathes deadly hornets?! Bullets are lethal no matter what you call them. We do not have the resources to fight these weapons. We should hide, not taunt them.”— Guardsman, Darryl Whitewall, “RV-4555D: Stop Tempting Fate” </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“我们不能忽视那个疯狂的先知口中有关毁灭的预言。他隐晦地提到了一场末日，但他的神明都是糟糕的武器。他预测他们将把殖民地变成废墟，只有悲伤的帝国行者将会在那里找到家园。我见过完人口中虽说的帝国行者，它就是一个加特林机枪和电弧导弹发射器的移动装置。哪怕完人称帝国行者在呼吸时都能释放出致命的黄蜂，又有谁在乎呢？！只要子弹足够致命，无论怎样叫都行。我们没有对抗这些武器的能力。我们应该做的是藏起来，而不是挑衅它们。”- 卫兵，达里尔·怀特沃尔，“RV-4555D：不要蔑视命运” </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8"><Data ss:Type="String">Edit: arc -&gt; Arc</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_STALLION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Imperial Buggy</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国越野车</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="255"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_STALLION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“Be careful, boys! There was a time when the Paragon had the best equipment money could buy. Don’t assume just because the Paragon are technically insane that their weapons won’t kill you just as dead as they could’ve when they were sane. That assault vehicle, the Imperial Buggy, is still a deadly one. It can deliver a punishing Laser Burst. It also has a mounted Laser gun repeater. Proceed with caution. If we’re lucky, we’ll convince them to sell their weapons to us, and we’ll have their power with us.”— Captain Addria Alethra, “RV-4456M: Encounters”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“小心点，小伙子们！有一段时间，完人拥有着金钱能够买到的最好武器。不要以为完人在技术上都是些疯子，就以为他们的武器没法杀了你，他们还没疯到那个程度。那辆突击载具 - 帝国越野车，就是一个非常致命的武器。它能够发射惩罚性激光脉冲，还搭载有连发激光枪。小心行事。如果我们足够幸运的话，就能说服他们将武器卖给我们，这样我们就能拥有同样的力量了。”- 阿德里亚·阿勒希拉队长，“RV-4456M：遭遇战”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8"><Data ss:Type="String">Modified names of the weaponry</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_LASER_TANK</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Imperial Behemoth</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国巨兽</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="255"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_LASER_TANK</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“The Paragons were the elite of the empire during the days of the Star Union. They would choose ominous names for their weaponry, often borrowing names from ancient books of religion and myth. They would then outfit their gear with devices that honored their gods, as they believed it inspired awe from common citizens.  In the case of the legendary Behemoth, its galvanized rounds have an incredible capacity to obliterate enemy machinery—a glorious tribute to their faith. That said, it’s really just a powerful tank with turret and cannon.”— Quinlinn T. Ortivexis, “RV-4388H: Historical Parallels: Humanity’s Twisted Past</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“在星际联盟时代，完人就是帝国的精英。他们会为自己的武器取一些凶狠的名字，一般都选自一些宗教和神话的古书。然后他们会用纪念神明的装置改造装备，他们相信这样能够对普通群众起到震慑作用。传奇的帝国巨兽就是一个例子。它装备有能够消灭敌人机器的电镀弹，这是对他们信仰的致敬。也就是说，它就是一辆装备着炮塔和加农炮的强大坦克。”- 奎里恩·T·奥迪威希斯，“RV-4388H：历史的相似之处：人类扭曲的过去”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8"><Data ss:Type="String">Edit: arc -&gt; Arc</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_APC</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Imperial APC</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝国 APC</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="285"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_APC</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“It was no secret. Old Sarge always assigned soldiers he thought had no potential to the Imperial APC. I’m not saying Sarge deserved his pranking, but when Malarkin got the assignment, he wanted revenge. The rugged old relic holds its own, but it’s clumsy. Without a few support drones, the thing is not going to win the respect of other soldiers. Its gun isn’t bad, but its old tech. In a support role, the thing is quite capable. I suppose that’s why we still drive them.” – Lieutenant Lenny Sasse, “RV-334M: Court-martial of Ensign Arnie Malarkin</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“这不是秘密。老萨尔基总是会将那些自己认为没有潜力的士兵分配至帝国自动相位控制战车。我并不是说萨尔基是在自食其果，但是当马拉尔金被分配到这个任务时，他想报复萨尔基。这粗糙的老遗产虽然结实，但是笨重不已。如果没有无人机的支援，它根本无法赢得其他士兵的尊重。搭载的枪械虽然性能尚可，但都是老旧技术。要说做些辅助工作，这东西还算不错，我想这也是我们仍然在使用它的原因。”- 中尉莱尼·萨希，“RV-334M：海军少尉阿尔尼·马拉尔金的军事法庭审判”</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_AUTO_TORPEDO</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Auto-torpedo</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">自动鱼雷</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="180"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPERIAL_AUTO_TORPEDO</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“Can’t fire a bomb at an enemy in the water. Missiles splash down, and then they’re gone. Bullets lose their oomph! We call it a missile if it flies through air, never mind the payload. Whether it holds incendiary or concussive explosives, a missile that travels through water is called a torpedo!” – Sergeant Charlie “Tugboat” Chase, “RV-6757M: Explosives and their Delivery Mechanisms.”</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“无法向水中的敌人投掷炸弹，导弹落入水中后就不见了，连子弹都失去了它们的活力！无论承载了多少爆炸物，只要在空中飞行的都被我们称为导弹。而无论装载着燃烧弹还是冲击炸药，只要在水中穿行的我们都称为鱼雷！”- 查理“拖船”沙斯中尉，“RV-6757M：爆炸物和其运输机制”</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">BLAZE_AUTO_TORPEDO</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Blaze Auto-torpedo</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">燃烧自动鱼雷</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PARAGON_HEAVY_DEFENSE_TURRET</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Warden Heavy Turret</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">典狱官重型炮台</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PARAGON_HEAVY_DEFENSE_TURRET</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Warden Heavy Turrets are often placed near defensive hardpoints to protect the Paragon Elite.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">典狱官重型炮台通常被放置在防御点附近，用来保护完人精英。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PARAGON_LIGHT_DEFENSE_TURRET</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Peacekeeper Light Turret</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">和平使者轻型炮塔</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PARAGON_LIGHT_DEFENSE_TURRET</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Peacekeeper Light Turrets are often used for suppression efforts by CORE and the Paragon Elite.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">核心和完人精英经常使用和平使者轻型炮塔进行火力压制。</Data></Cell></Row></Table><WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"><Unsynced/><Print><ValidPrinterInfo/><HorizontalResolution>600</HorizontalResolution><VerticalResolution>600</VerticalResolution></Print><Zoom>115</Zoom><Selected/><TopRowVisible>29</TopRowVisible><Panes><Pane><Number>3</Number><ActiveRow>36</ActiveRow><ActiveCol>3</ActiveCol></Pane></Panes><ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects><ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios></WorksheetOptions></Worksheet></Workbook>