<?xml version="1.0"?><?mso-application progid="Excel.Sheet"?><Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel" xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40"><DocumentProperties xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"><Author>Tom Bird</Author><LastAuthor>Glenn Smits</LastAuthor><LastPrinted>2019-08-01T11:36:28Z</LastPrinted><Created>2019-05-07T15:06:48Z</Created><LastSaved>2019-08-08T12:16:01Z</LastSaved><Version>16.00</Version></DocumentProperties><OfficeDocumentSettings xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"><AllowPNG/></OfficeDocumentSettings><ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"><WindowHeight>9750</WindowHeight><WindowWidth>13170</WindowWidth><WindowTopX>32767</WindowTopX><WindowTopY>32767</WindowTopY><ProtectStructure>False</ProtectStructure><ProtectWindows>False</ProtectWindows></ExcelWorkbook><Styles><Style ss:ID="Default" ss:Name="Normal"><Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/><Borders/><Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="11" ss:Color="#000000"/><Interior/><NumberFormat/><Protection/></Style><Style ss:ID="s62"><Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom" ss:WrapText="1"/></Style><Style ss:ID="s63"><Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom" ss:WrapText="1"/><Interior/></Style><Style ss:ID="s64"><Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom" ss:WrapText="1"/><Font ss:FontName="Arial" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Color="#000000"/></Style><Style ss:ID="s65"><Font ss:FontName="Arial" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Color="#000000"/></Style></Styles><Worksheet ss:Name="Script"><Table x:FullColumns="1" x:FullRows="1" ss:DefaultColumnWidth="51.75" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15"><Column ss:Width="139.5"/><Column ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="251.25"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="317.25"/><Column ss:Width="147.75"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="262.5"/><Column ss:StyleID="s62" ss:Width="120"/><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SURVEYING_UNIQUE</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">The DEV TEAM / MISC NOTES column contains info on what text between { } signs means (if applicable). It usually stands for either a numeric value, or a numeric value with an icon. Text between [ ] signs stands for a certain type of icon. </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SCENE ID</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TEXT ID</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ENGLISH STRING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCALIZED STRING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ALTERNATIVE ENGLISH STRING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">ALTERNATIVE LOCALIZED STRING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCALIZATION NOTES</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DEV TEAM / MISC NOTES</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">UNIQUE_SURVEY_SITE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Large Anomalous Site</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">大型异常地点</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="33.5625"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">UNIQUE_SURVEY_SITE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">This anomalous site can be explored by a hero to recover research data and reveal secrets of the Star Union.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">该异常地点可由一名英雄进行探索，从而恢复研究数据并揭露星际联盟的秘密。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Lost Legion</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">失落的军团</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="34.6875"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A massive Paragon estate, guarded by a static legion of Paragon soldiers.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">一个庞大的完人庄园，由一群静止的完人士兵保护着。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Paragon are an in game faction</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="89.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FIRST_RESULT_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">While setting up the perfect selfie, we stumbled upon a vast subterranean ruined city. Descending into a vertical airshaft, we located a well-preserved Paragon estate, still properly shielded. Just outside the safety of the secured perimeter, and powerful ranks of shield troopers stood in formation, unmoving as though frozen in stasis. Legions of elite Paragon forces arrayed in all their impressive power encircled the estate, doing nothing, standing perfectly still.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当我们正在挑选完美的自拍角度时，我们偶然发现了一个巨大的地下遗迹古城。我们从一个通风竖井下去后，发现了一个保存完好的完人庄园，庄园里仍然有一定的保护措施。就在安全警戒线的外围，一队强大的带盾步兵一动不动地站着，仿佛被冻住了一样。另外还有一群威风凛凛的精英完人部队环绕而立守护着庄园，但也只是静静站着。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="150"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The legion remained transfixed as we passed. The shielded gate swung aside with a deafening hiss. Just beyond, a Paragon Governor greeted us with weapons trained in our direction. His augments were immaculate, and his hands crackled as he discharged a surge of energy through powerful implants. The arc of energy was a warning shot. Elite soldiers in perfect working order stood beside him, targeting us with their weapons. They regarded us as though not aware of the Star Union's fall, nor that they live in a ruin.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当我们经过时，完人军团仍旧保持着静止。突然，大门随着一声震耳欲聋的嘶嘶声摇晃到一边。就在不远处，一位完人总督拿着武器面对着我们。他的强化装备非常完美，强大的植入物释放出庞大的能量，双手也随之发出噼啪的响声。然而，这样的能量弧闪动只是一个警告信号而已。全副武装的精英士兵站在他身旁，用武器对准了我们。他们对待我们的方式，仿佛不知道星际联盟已经衰落了一样，不仅如此，他们好像也没有意识到他们自己生活在废墟之中。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="26.4375"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Perform the Vanguard Greeting Protocol</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">执行先锋问候协议</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Conducting the Vanguard Greeting Protocol according to doctrine</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在根据教义执行先锋问候协议</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="150"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We hailed the Paragon with codes given to our expedition. Recognition flickered like a smile in the Governor's expression, and he explained that a Synthesis AI weapon named NEKRIS has besieged them for over a century, turning his troops into mindless drones. Decade after decade, they retreated into an ever-smaller shielded area as the city fell block by block. The Governor looked to us to assist them and destroy NEKRIS to free him and his men from their tyranny.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们根据探险队获得的代码向这位完人表示了问候。完人总督仿佛露出微笑似的表示了认可，他解释道，一个名叫“奈克里斯”的人工智能合成武器包围了他们一个多世纪，把他的部队变成了没有意识的机器。时间不断流逝，城市不断陷落，他们不得不撤退到越来越小的隐蔽区域之中。总督希望我们能帮助他们消灭奈克里斯，把他和他的部下从暴政中解放出来。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Let our diplomats diffuse the situation </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">让我们的外交官来化解危机 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Our diplomats are negotiating with the ancient Paragon Governor</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的外交官正在与古老的完人总督协商</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Our diplomats found that traditional greetings alleviated their alarmed state. The Paragon leader explained his predicament. For over a century, an AI weapon codenamed NEKRIS, capable of seizing control of cybernetics, assaulted their city. Little by little, the governor's forces withdrew. He lost territory to its relentless advance. He claimed NEKRIS was a Synthesis tool that objected to his affiliation with CORE. He gestured to his frozen legions and begged us to find NEKRIS and set them free.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的外交官发现传统的问候能够缓解他们的警觉，完人首领解释了他所处的困境。原来在这一个多世纪以来，一个代号为“奈克里斯”的人工智能武器控制了神经机械，袭击了他们的城市。在这场战斗中，总督的部队不断撤退，人工智能武器无情地发动进攻，不断夺走他们城市的领土。总督说，奈克里斯是一种合成工具，反对他与“核心”的联系。他指着自己冰冻的军团，请求我们找到奈克里斯，让他们重获自由。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Attack the Governor and loot the estate</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">攻击总督，洗劫庄园</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The governor scoffs at your brazen insult, and with a short, dignified gesture, orders his men to engage. Paragon Guard immediately form a protective wall between us and the governor as his other men dart for cover, ready to engage!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">总督对你厚颜无耻的侮辱嗤之以鼻，他下达了一段简短而威严的命令让部下应战。完人守卫立即在我们和总督之间形成了一道防护墙，其他士兵则迅速寻找掩护，准备与我们交战！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Paragon Elite troops stand at the gate of a Paragon estate, guarding their master zealously, prepared to repel any invader.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">完人精英部队守在庄园的门口，一心一意地保护他们的主人，准备击退所有入侵者。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">With the Governor and his elite guard defeated, our troops swiftly turned to looting the estate, finding much of value. Most notable amongst the findings was a vast library, a database containing classified information of all kinds. Our scientists recovered a wealth of useful knowldge!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">击败总督和他的精英护卫后，我们的部队迅速洗劫了庄园并且发现了很多宝物。其中最值得注意的发现是一个巨大的图书馆，这里是一个含有各种机密信息的数据库。我们的科学家发现了大量有用的知识！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_4_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Let the Paragon vouch for us</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">让完人来为我们担保</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_4_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Negotiating with Paragon assistance</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在完人的帮助下进行协商</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="150"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_4_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We already knew the Paragon were willing to diffuse the situation, and the governor of the underground ruin told us his story. He and his city were isolated nearly a century ago by a Synthesis AI weapon codenamed NEKRIS. It commandeered his legions and pushed his forces deeper into the city center. The Paragon asked for our assistance in fighting NEKRIS so that they may all be set free.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们知道完人想要化解这场危机，那位地下废墟中的总督也告诉了我们关于他的故事：将近一个世纪之前，一个代号为“奈克里斯”的人工智能合成武器隔绝了他和他的城市，他不得不率领他的军团来到了城市中心。完人总督请求我们帮助他与奈克里斯作战，让他们重获自由。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">As the gate closed behind us, we looked around us at the ruins. There were decayed Paragon legions scattered all around the city. NEKRIS could have been hiding in any of them. We were fortunate to have made it to the center without being attacked, but now we feel strangely trapped. We assembled some equipment and prepared for an ambush. Our presence alone was apparently not enough to trigger the NEKRIS daemon's hostility matrices. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">随着大门在我们身后关上，我们在废墟中四处观望。整个城市都遍布着腐烂的完人军团，奈克里斯可能藏在任何一个地方。幸运的是，我们在没有受到攻击的情况下抵达了城市中心，然而我们却感觉好像进入了某个陷阱之中。我们组装了一些设备，准备迎接伏击。看来，光是站在这里显然不足以触发奈克里斯精灵的敌意矩阵。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Find and destroy NEKRIS manually</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">使用人力找到并消灭奈克里斯</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="90"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We march over the path, troops inspecting the fallen cybernetic legions for signs of the virus. Suddenly, several of the troops awaken. Network activity spikes as their eyes lock onto us. Soldiers move to defend the network monitor. NEKRIS is on the move! We must destroy the hosts around it to prevent its escape. Deprive it of hosts and it will fall!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们沿着道路向前行进，部队一路检查着倒下的神经机械军团，寻找病毒的迹象。突然，网络活动激增，几个士兵醒了过来，眼睛直勾勾地盯着我们，随后纷纷前去保护网络监控器。看来，奈克里斯开始行动了！我们必须消灭它周围的宿主，防止它逃脱。只要它脱离了宿主，一切就结束了！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NEKRIS certainly senses our mission, for it awakened the statuesque soldiers to attack us. It is spreading through them, activating them one by one. We must act quickly or they will all be lost, and this terrible weapon will attempt to escape.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">奈克里斯肯定察觉到了我们的意图，所以唤醒了雕像般的士兵来攻击我们。它在这些士兵间扩散，一个接一个地激活他们。我们必须迅速行动，否则所有的士兵都将被奈克里斯控制，而它也将逃之夭夭。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="105"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">As the last of the infected troopers fell, NEKRIS fell with it, losing its grip on all the frozen legions. It seems these soldiers were decayed well beyond a salvageable point, mind scrambled by the enemy AI weapon. Our researchers, after a quick study of the remnants of NEKRIS and its effect on the troopers, have uncovered new insights into computing and cybernetics!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当最后一个受到感染的士兵倒下后，奈克里斯也消亡了，冰冻军团的控制也随之解除。然而，这些士兵似乎已经腐烂到了无法回收的地步，心智也被这个人工智能武器扰乱了。我们的研究人员在迅速研究了奈克里斯的残骸及其对士兵的影响之后，对计算和神经机械有了新的发现！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="86.4375"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Use a Synthesis Daemon to lure out and attempt to capture NEKRIS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">使用合成精灵引诱并尝试捕获奈克里斯</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Our hackers infuse the nearest troopers with a modified Countermeasure Daemon. It swiftly possesses and purges the stunned trooper of compromised decision circuits. It propagates from troop to troop, countering the damage done by NEKRIS and removing its ability to control the legions. Suddenly, several of the troops awaken, their eyes locked onto us. NEKRIS knows we are to blame. It is trying to physically counteract our attempts to control it. The awakened troopers move to destroy us. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的黑客给附近的士兵注入了一个改造过的反制精灵，它迅速地控制了这些昏迷的士兵，并清除了他们体内受损的决策电路。反制精灵在部队间传播，抵消了奈克里斯造成的伤害，并移除了它对军团的控制。突然，几个士兵醒了过来，眼睛直勾勾地盯着我们。奈克里斯知道了我们干的事情，并移除了我们反制精灵对士兵的控制。苏醒的士兵走了过来，准备消灭我们。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="90"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Unfortunately, our Countermeasure Daemon is detected and we cannot move quickly enough to counter NEKRIS's defenses. We must fight the activated troopers to give our Countermeasure Daemon time to nullify the rest of NEKRIS's control.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">不幸的是，奈克里斯检测到了我们的反制精灵，而我们却无法迅速反应应对它的防御。我们必须与这些激活的部队战斗，给我们的反制精灵足够的时间来解除奈克里斯剩余的控制。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="90"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We did it! Fighting the troopers gave our Countermeasure Daemon time to spring its trap. NEKRIS is trapped in a single disabled system. It cannot activate its own control circuits thanks to our clever hackers and mad coding skills. Our Hackers get to work disassembling the NEKRIS's core subroutines and examining its exotic code features. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们成功了！与这些士兵战斗给了反制精灵足够的时间触发陷阱，奈克里斯被困在了一个瘫痪的系统中。多亏了我们聪明的黑客和复杂的编码技术，奈克里斯再也无法激活自己的控制电路了。我们的黑客开始分解奈克里斯的核心子程序，研究它奇特的代码特性。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="90"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Use an EMP to thin out NEKRIS's potential hosts</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">使用 EMP 清除奈克里斯的潜在宿主</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="90"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We discharged an EMP to disable the most immediate threat, only to discover NEKRIS was backed up in some of the more shielded implants. It is moving to counter our hostile attack with its own version of hostility. The Paragon troopers lurch forward and begin discharging their weapons!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们释放了一阵 EMP 破坏了最直接的威胁，却发现奈克里斯竟然被一些保护植物覆盖着。它正采取行动反制我们的攻击，完人士兵踉跄着向前走来，并且掏出了他们的武器！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="90"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NEKRIS is on the move, searching for our threats and eliminating any hostile entities in the area--in this case, anything that breathes. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">奈克里斯开始行动了。它正在寻找我们布下的威胁，准备消灭地区中所有的敌对实体，也就是要消灭任何有生命的东西。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="105"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">As the last of the infected troopers falls, NEKRIS is left bound in the body of a decayed and damaged cybernetic servo, twitching with frustration. Unfortunately, none of the troopers is salvageable, having decayed beyond the point of repair, but the remnants of NEKRIS will serve our researchers quite well. We will dissect it shortly. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">最后一个受感染的士兵倒下后，奈克里斯被困在了一个腐烂受损的神经机械伺服器中，沮丧地抽搐着。不幸的是，所有的士兵都腐烂到了无法修复的地步，已经无法回收了，但奈克里斯的残骸还是能够为我们的研究人员服务。我们将很快对它进行剖析。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="135"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Returning to the Governor, the Paragon hailed us with gratitude. He kept unconciously pawing at his own cybernetic implants, as if not quite believing that the threat to his being had ended. True to his word, he renounced his love of CORE and promised his fealty to us. He then addressed us, asking us quite pointedly why we came to this world in the first place.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当我们回到总督身边时，完人在感激中向我们致敬。总督在不知不觉间始终摆弄着自己的神经机械植入物，似乎不太相信自己族人受到的威胁已经结束了。他信守诺言，宣布放弃追随“核心”，承诺对我们效忠。随后，他非常有目的性地询问了我们来到这个星球的初衷。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">To conquer this world</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">为了征服这个世界</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Governor shook his head wearily and said, "There's never enough world for that type of ambition, but we will aide you nonetheless." His elite troopers fell into formation behind him, and their implants suddenly took on the appearance of our own insignias.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">总督厌倦地摇了摇头，说：“就算征服所有的世界也都无法满足这样的野心。但无论怎样，我们还是会帮助你。”他的精英部队在他身后排好队形，植入物突然呈现出我们徽章的模样。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">To bring peace to this world</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">为了给这个世界带来和平</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Governor gave a half grin and stated, "The only true peace is the extinction of sentience. Life is nothing but conflict." Finding his answer unnerving, we countered that our way of life is far superior and more evolved than his. He nodded and offered to help train our diplomatic envoys in the detailed nature of civil discourse and universal greetings. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">总督露出了一个似是而非的微笑，说：“唯一的和平来自于感知的灭亡。生命本身就是一种冲突。”他的回答令人不安，我们反驳道我们的生活方式远比他优越，也比他更先进。他点了点头，表示愿意帮助训练我们的外交使节，让他们了解公民对话和普遍问候的详细本质。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">To uncover secrets of the past</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">为了揭露过去的秘密</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Governor nodded and then stated with a laugh, "So you do not wish to sleep well?" We didn't quite know how to respond, but he reassured us that he has a vast library of technology and research projects from the past, and that part of his previous duties entailed maintaining Star Union projects and secrets. He offered his vast stores of understanding to us.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">总督点点头，然后笑着说：“这么说，你们不想睡个好觉了？”我们不知道应该如何回应，但他向我们保证，他掌握着大量与以前的技术和研究项目有关的信息。毕竟，他曾经的职责之一就是维护星际联盟的项目和机密。他向我们提供了大量的信息。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">COUNTERMEASURE_DEAMON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Countermeasure Daemon</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">反制精灵</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">COUNTERMEASURE_DEAMON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Daemon we unleashed among the frozen legion is eliminating hosts one by one. Every [turn/], {Killcount} unawakened soldier is destroyed.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们在冰冻军团中释放的精灵正在一个接一个地消灭宿主。每 [turn/]，都有 {Killcount} 个未苏醒的士兵被消灭。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FORGOTTEN_EMP_COMBAT_EFFECT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">EMP</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">EMP</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FORGOTTEN_EMP_COMBAT_EFFECT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The EMP we prepared is ready to detonate and will wipe out {KillCount} potential hosts.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的 EMP 已准备就绪，将会消灭 {KillCount} 个潜在的宿主。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">GOVERNORS_BOON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Forgotten Paragon's boon</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">被遗忘的完人恩惠</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_FORGOTTEN_PARAGON</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SIDE_EFFECT_ESTATE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The sector gains the [abilityblue]Paragon Estate[/abilityblue] feature.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">该区域获得[abilityblue]完人庄园[/abilityblue]特征。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Reality Anchor</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">现实之锚</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">A timeless Voidtech facility. A gate is found that leads to a facility built in a different dimension entirely, a gateway to the earliest successes of Voidtech development</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">一个不受时间影响的虚空科技设施。我们发现了一个门道，通向一个完全不同维度的设施，这里是虚空科技最早成功开发的入口。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FIRST_RESULT_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We discovered a pocket dimension hidden in a subterranean complex. A veritable fortress gate looms within it. Clearly Voidtech in origin, a crackling energy device whirs at the gate's center. At the foot of the gate, armed Echo Walkers stand with weapons trained against a horde of Psi-Fish. The Psi-Fish are trying to enter the gate.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们在地下建筑群中发现了一个隐藏的秀珍维度，一扇真实的堡垒大门在其中若隐若现。显然，这是一种虚空科技，某种能量设备正在大门的中心呼呼作响。在大门下面，一群全副武装的回声行者正拿着武器站在那里与一群灵能水母对峙。灵能水母试图闯进大门。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The battle must be resolved. It's a simple decision between joining the Voidtech defenders or helping the Psi-Fish reach the gate.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们必须解决这场战斗。这是一个再简单不过的决定了，选择加入虚空科技防守者，还是选择帮助灵能水母抵达大门。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Take advantage of this assault and attack the Echo Walkers</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">把握这次袭击机会，攻击回声行者</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">The Psi-Fish must be capable of telepathy or something, because they immediately stand aside as if they can read our minds. The Echo Walkers train their weapons on us now. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">灵能水母一定有着某种心灵感应之类的能力，它们立刻站在了我们身旁，好像能读懂我们的心思一样。现在，回声行者将武器对准了我们。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">The Echo Walkers stand guard to defend the gate, while the Psi-Fish are ready to help us break through the Voidtech defenses.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">回声行者守卫着大门，灵能水母则准备帮助我们突破这里的虚空科技防御。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The Psi-Fish were delighted by our help, filling our bodies with sensations of ecstasy and delight. In our minds, we all sensed gratitude and something vague about how delicious our brains felt. They give us a gift before proceeding on through the gate. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">灵能水母对我们的帮助感到高兴，我们的身体感受到了它们的狂喜和愉悦之情。我们在脑海中感觉到了灵能水母的感激之情，还模糊地感觉到了它们对我们大脑美味的看法。它们在通过大门之前给了我们一份礼物。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Help the Phase Walkers defend against the Psifish</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帮助回声行者对抗灵能水母</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">The Echo Walkers nod as though they're familiar with this scene and knew it would come. Ironically, we can't surprise the Psi-Fish with our intention of ambush either, as they can read our intentions. They turn dark red in color and prepare to defend themselves.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">回声行者点了点头，好像他们熟悉非常这个场景并知道这一切会发生似的。讽刺的是，我们也无法向灵能水母发动袭击，因为它们能够读懂我们的心思。它们的颜色变得深红无比，准备进行防卫。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Psi-Fish swirl angrily, emanating waves of fear and revulsion at our decision to interfere in their business. The Echo Walkers cautiously watch as we approach. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">灵能水母愤怒地旋转起来，对我们干预它们的事情表示厌恶，发出了一股令人恐惧的波动。回声行者谨慎地看着我们接近。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">The Echo Walkers returned to their posts, nodding gratefully that the hostile psychic entities were dealt with. There was a loud pop, and before us appeared a small gift enclosed in fancy Voidtech packaging. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">回声行者回到了他们的岗位上，感激地点了点头，对我们帮助他们消灭了灵能水母表示满意。随着砰的一声巨响，我们面前出现了一个小礼物，包裹着精美的虚空科技。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">As we approached the gate, a loud voice boomed, "What makes you worthy of the Reality Gate?" A massive eye emerged from the warbling energies, narrowing its focus on us expectantly. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">在我们接近大门时，一声巨大的声音突然响起：“你凭什么能够进入现实之门？”一只巨大的眼睛从颤抖的能量中浮现出来，期待地凝视着我们。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="31.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Try the phrase "Hail our Penguin overlords"</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">试着说一句“企鹅领主万岁”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Communicating with the entity in the Reality Anchor…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在与现实之锚中的实体沟通…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="43.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT_SUCCESS</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Humored, the automated entity jittered and skipped. For a moment, a dozen flux images of possible realities cycled before us, before an Ethereal Penguin emerged, under our command, granting us access to its energy stores. Who would have thought that this universe really likes penguins?</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">有趣的是，这个自动化实体摇摇晃晃地走了起来。过了一会儿，十几幅可能的现实片段在我们面前不断循环，直到一只虚灵企鹅出现。在我们的命令下，它允许我们进入能量库。谁会想到这个宇宙真的这么喜欢企鹅呢？</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="41.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT_FAILURE</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The automated eye blinked, then rolled upwards and jittered as though having a seizure. A shower of sparks coughed from the gateway as dozens of realities flashed within. None of the images stay long, as though none of them quite fit our request. With its energy stores depleted, we eventually gained access to the gates.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">它眨了眨机械的眼睛，突然眼皮向上翻去，好像癫痫发作一样地抖动着。一道火花从大门里迸射了出来，大量现实的片段开始闪现，所有的影像停留的时间都很短，似乎没有一张适合。随着能量逐渐枯竭，我们最终进入了大门。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Enter the gate under Voidtech code Sigma-Chimera-45</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">输入虚空科技代码“西格玛-奇美拉-45”进入大门</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The code granted us access as Voidtech scientists. The gateway is full of energy reserves, which is now open to us. It also granted us full access to a time-controlling assistant known simply as a Phase Manipulator. We all laughed at the idea of such a simple label for the complexity of time, as though it were merely a phase of reality?!  </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">这串代码赋予了我们虚空科技科学家的身份来进入大门。大门中充满了能量储备，现在这些都是我们的了。这串代码还赋予了我们对一个时间控制辅助器的完全使用权限，也就是我们所说的相位操纵器。用这样一个简单的标签来表示时间的复杂性，我们都感到非常可笑，仿佛它只是现实的一面而已？！  </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Ask scientists to bypass the gate</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">让科学家绕过大门</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The scientists are working on the gate and the entity within…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">科学家正在研究大门和里面的实体…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Using our depth of scientific knowledge, we resorted to the age-old theory known as "pull the plug". We know that even a gate of significant complexity cannot function without a connection to its energy reserves. So we drained them first, rendering the gate compliant, and the extra energy is always a welcome prize.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">利用我们科学知识的深度，我们决定使用一种名为“拔掉插头”的古老理论。我们都知道，如果大门失去了能量储备的连接，就算它再是复杂也无法发挥作用。因此我们抽干了能量，让大门失去了能量输送。再说了，我们永远也不会拒绝获得额外的能量。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="96"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Beyond the gate, we found a reality-branching Julia-bridge, leading to a multi-dimensional rift nexus. Floating in the space between, like a cloud of sorrow, we saw the remains of bodies and fragments of armor. Clearly, many expeditions have failed in their mission, and these are the remnants of their catastrophe. Further exploration would be dangerous, but stabilizing such a rift could be quite a find for the empire.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">在大门另一边，我们发现了一座分离现实的茱莉亚大桥，通向某个多维度裂隙节点。我们看到尸体的残骸和盔甲的碎片像乌云一样漂浮在两个空间之间。显然，许多探险队都没能通过这里，眼前的景象就是他们遭遇灾祸的残余。看来进一步探索将会非常危险，但如果能稳定这样一个裂隙，对帝国来说也会是一个相当不错的发现。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">We can use the gate to provide Echo Walker support in combat!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们可以利用大门在战斗中为回声行者提供支援！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">By cross coupling the phase capacitance in the Julia-bridge, our scientists were able to stabilize the reality gate's echo operations. We can now deploy it in tactical operations. Science: what can't it do?</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">通过对茱莉亚大桥实施电容性的交叉耦合，我们的科学家稳定了现实之门的回声操作。现在，我们可以在战术行动中部署它了。还有什么是科学没法做到的吗？</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Preparing the gate for Voidtech Echo Walker support…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在为支援虚空科技回声行者准备大门…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">It is our duty to find and rescue those lost expeditions!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们有责任找到并拯救那些失踪的探险队！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="52.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We braved the random uncertainty of the high probability of certain death, and found the lost Voidtech expeditions trapped in a recursive dimensional fold. The Voidtech engineers, delighted by our foolish bravery, set to rectifying the issues with causality. By looping the trailing rift tentrites back upon themselves in an array of cycling maglev rings, we converted the Julia-bridge into a Voidtech landmark. They then rewound spacetime to retrieve the splattered expeditions, and a colony of grateful citizens reforms before our eyes.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们冒着极高的死亡风险，找到了失踪的虚空科技探险队，他们被困在了一个循环的维度折叠之中。虚空科技的工程师们对我们鲁莽的勇气感到高兴，他们找到了问题的原因并进行了纠正。我们将蔓延的裂缝绕成一圈，形成了一条循环的磁悬浮环，把茱莉亚大桥转变成了一个虚空科技地标。随后，他们倒转了时空，还原了那场惊险血腥的探险，一群心怀感激的居民在我们眼前重新组合了起来。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_REALITY_ANCHOR</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rescuing the interdimensional survivors…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">拯救跨维度中的幸存者…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tyre's Tomb</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">泰尔之墓</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="54"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">A tomb of ornate wonder. The finely detailed golden tomb is believed to be final resting place of the great Es'Teq Lord Oreus Tyre.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">一个充满奇迹的华丽墓穴。相传，这座精致的金色陵墓是伟大的埃斯特克领主奥瑞厄斯·泰尔最后的安息之地。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FIRST_RESULT_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We've uncovered a tomb of ornate wonder. The detailed filigree of flowers and vines, birds and strange creatures, twist up and around the entrance of this ancient tomb. All is covered in finely hammered gold leaf. The fact that the gold has not been stripped away bodes well for this expedition. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们发现了一座充满奇迹的华丽墓穴。花鸟藤蔓以及奇怪生物制成的金银丝线装饰着古墓的入口，所有的东西都覆盖着铸打而成的精致金箔。这里的黄金还未被夺走，这对这次探险来说是个好兆头。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="65.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">There are few clues emblazoned upon the gate, but judging from the fixation on once-living creatures, and the joyous nature of the carvings, the whole place represents Es'Teq mythology. The Es'Teq believe the mind of man was meant to be immortal, and that the Creator intended life to live on forever. A strange device stands in front of the gate, about the size of a hand. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">大门上纹饰的线索很少，但从这里对过去生物的迷恋以及充满了欢乐本性的雕刻来看，整个地方都代表着埃斯特克的色彩。埃斯特克人相信，人的心灵是不朽的，造物主希望生命能够永存。大门前放着一个奇怪的装置，大小和一只手掌差不多大。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">As a hero of my people, I must bear this burden</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">身为我族人的英雄，我必须肩负这一重任</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bearing the burden for the legacy of the Es'Teq…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在承担埃斯特克的遗产…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="43.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Our hero approached the device and placed a palm onto the strange surface. It hummed to life, and our hero was racked with terrible pain. Our troops watched in sympathy, but could do nothing to prevent the gate from taking its due. It is the nature of a hero to bear the pain of the people. A chime sounded, and the tomb door activated, revealing a chamber beyond.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的英雄走近这个装置，将手掌放在装置奇怪的表面之上。突然，装置发出嗡嗡的声音运转起来，英雄遭受了某种可怕的痛苦。我们其他人只能关切地看着，无法阻止这扇大门拿走它应得的东西。替人民承受痛苦是英雄的职责。接着，一阵钟声响起，墓穴大门缓缓打开，露出了里面的房间。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Make the troops bear the burden</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">让部队肩负这一重任</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">As the device was activated, the whole crowd swooned with weakness. It is was though our very living essence is pulled from us, and we all stumbled and struggled to stay on our feet. After what felt like an eternity of torture, the device activated and the tomb entrance swung open, revealing a chamber within.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">激活设备后，所有人都因虚弱而感到一阵眩晕，仿佛我们的精华全都被抽离了一样，但我们还是挣扎着站了起来。在经历了一场仿佛无穷无尽的折磨之后，我们激活了这个装置，墓穴的入口也随之打开，露出了里面的房间。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="55.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">A large chamber lined with crystalline machinery glowed faintly. The walls were lined with an assembly line for constructing tools to serve the tomb guardians. The Golemforge, a construction for creating Es'Teq Golems sprawls through this chamber. It is well-known that every Es'Teq tomb is guarded, and like bas-relief leaping to life figures float from the walls to intercept our explorers. There is a moment of pause as the Drained make their way around the equipment to approach us.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">偌大的房间中整齐地摆放着一些微微发光的水晶机器，墙壁上排列着用来建造工具为墓穴守护者服务的装配线。一座用来建造埃斯特克魔像的巨大建筑：魔像熔炉横亘在这个房间之中。众所周知，每座埃斯特克古墓都有守卫把守，他们就像是墙壁上雕刻的浮雕一跃变成了有生命的生物一样，拦住了我们这些探险者。当枯萎者绕过设备靠近我们时，他们停顿了片刻。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Destroy these abominations</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">消灭这些令人憎恶的生物</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We prepare to fight an assortment of Drained and their strange tomb guardians.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们已准备好与枯萎者和怪异的墓穴守卫战斗。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The tomb guardians lurk ready to stop our intrusion. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">墓穴守护者潜伏着准备阻止我们的入侵。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="72"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The Drained guardians fell. Their last words shook in our minds, like the prayers of the damned--futile and faithless, they crumbled to dust. The Golemforge fell silent. Golems built in this chamber would have had to be infused with essence to be of any use. The only source of essence most likely lies deeper within this tomb. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">枯萎守护者倒下了。他们的遗言震动着我们的心灵，就像那些被诅咒之人的祷告一样，徒劳而不忠。最后，他们化为了尘土，魔像熔炉也陷入了沉寂。这个房间里建造的魔像必须使用精华才能发挥作用，而唯一的精华之源很有可能就位于这座墓穴的深处。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">They seem to bear no hostile intent... Try to communicate</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">他们似乎没有敌意…试着与他们沟通</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="34.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Communicating with the Drained….</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在与枯萎者沟通…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="122.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The Drained guardians fell. Their last words shook in our minds, like the prayers of the damned--futile and faithless, they crumbled to dust. The Golemforge fell silent. Golems built in this chamber would have had to be infused with essence to be of any use. The only source of essence most likely lies deeper within this tomb. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">枯萎守护者倒下了。他们的遗言震动着我们的心灵，就像那些被诅咒之人的祷告一样，徒劳而不忠。最后，他们化为了尘土，魔像熔炉也陷入了沉寂。这个房间里建造的魔像必须使用精华才能发挥作用，而唯一的精华之源很有可能就位于这座墓穴的深处。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">As an Es'Teq Prophet, they must submit to me</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">身为埃斯特克的先知，他们必须服从于我</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="124.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The Drained paused and bowed when they noticed we are willing to communicate rather than mindlessly attack them. They explained that their High Lord 'Oreus Tyre' gave his being to save them from the Rot that was overtaking the tomb. The tomb was cleansed, and the Drained were saved, but the High Lord still bore the Rot's corruption within himself. They have offered an item if we would enter the tomb's heart and save their High Lord. It's an artifact for cleaning Rot.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当枯萎者发现我们愿意与他们交流而不是盲目地发动攻击时，他们停下了脚步并向我们鞠了一躬。枯萎者解释说，他们的至高领主奥瑞厄斯·泰尔献出了自己的生命拯救了他们，让他们免遭墓穴腐败的影响。墓穴得到了净化，他们也因此获得了拯救，但那位至尊领主却仍然被腐败所吞噬。枯萎者提出，如果我们能进入墓穴的中心并拯救他们的至尊领主，他们将赠予我们一个可以净化腐坏的神器。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="79.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We entered the cavernous tomb's heart. A rusty stream of Rot turns the essence flows a sickly red. On the platform at the top of the corrupted stream floats what is left of Oreus Tyre. He is no longer an entity we would recognize, but is now a dark god of terrible malice and entropic spite known as "The Eater of the Dead". </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们进入了巨大墓穴的中心，一股铁锈般的腐坏之流将精华变成了病态的红色。奥瑞厄斯·泰尔的残余躯体漂浮在腐坏之流顶部的平台上。他已经不再是我们能够辨认出的一个实体，而是一个充满了憎恶和混沌恶意的黑暗之神 - 食尸者。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Engage the Corrupted High-Lord</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">与堕落的至尊领主交战</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="58.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">As we move to the platform to engage the monstrous thing that Oreus has become, the golem statues lining the walkway awaken, shining red with crimson Rot. Oreus Tyre awakens from his trance. He unleashes a deafening roar. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当我们走上祭坛准备与奥瑞厄斯变成的怪物战斗时，走道两旁的魔像雕塑突然苏醒了过来，散发着猩红的腐坏之光。奥瑞厄斯·泰尔从沉睡中清醒，发出了一声震耳欲聋的吼叫。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="48"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The Eater of the Dead descends to attack, his golem servants eager to drain us of our living essence. They desire the life we take for granted. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">食尸者走了下来向我们发起了攻击，他的魔像仆人也渴望榨干我们的生命精华，渴望夺走我们习以为常的生命。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The corrupted High Lord faltered along with the golems that guarded him. The hideous creature screamed in pain, and then fell silent, defeated.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">堕落的至尊领主和守卫他的魔像倒下了。那个可怕的生物痛苦地尖叫着，接着一切归于寂静，我们打败他了。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Find a weakness in the golems using the Golemforge</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">利用魔像熔炉找出魔像的弱点</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="26.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Finding a weakness in the golems using the Golemforge…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在利用魔像熔炉找出魔像的弱点…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="88.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The corrupted High Lord faltered, the Rot-corrupted essence of his being still flowing within the construct... The hideous creature screamed in pain, and then fell silent, defeated.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">堕落的至尊领主倒下了，腐坏的精华在墓穴里流淌…那个可怕的生物痛苦地尖叫着，接着一切归于寂静，我们打败他了。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="44.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Oreus Tyre lies helpless on the ground. His corrupted form sprawls before us, hungrily opened to take life from any who are foolish enough to give it. The artifact could be used on Oreus, but what do we really owe him? We could use this artifact to repair the tomb itself and use the equipment here to build Forgotten units. The temptation of choice is why we are alive. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">奥瑞厄斯·泰尔无助地躺在地上，他那腐朽的形态在我们面前蔓延开来，饥渴地想要夺取任何愚蠢之人的生命。我们将那件神器用在奥瑞厄斯身上，但我们又欠他什么呢？我们可以用这件神器来修复墓穴，并用这里的装备来建造被遗忘者单位，如此充满诱惑的选择才能护我们安全。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Use the artifact to save Oreus Tyre</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">使用神器拯救奥瑞厄斯·泰尔</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="58.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We used the artifact to save Oreus Tyre, purifying his being. The ancient Es'Teq Lord stirs, pushing his way out of the horrible construct in which he was confined, rising in a new form. He is grateful, and offers to join our cause to repay the debt he owes us.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们用神器拯救了奥瑞厄斯·泰尔，净化了他的身体。这位古老的埃斯特克领主微微地颤抖了一下，摆脱了他可怕的样貌，以一种全新的形态站了起来。他十分感激，并提出加入我们的事业来偿还我们的救命之恩。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Use the artifact to purify the tomb</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">使用神器净化墓穴</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="84"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Oreus can blow in the Void. We focus the power of the artifact on cleansing the Es'Teq tomb. The artifact loses its strength, but combined with the broken High Lord's power, the monolithic structure purges the poisonous Rot and glows turquoise with life essence again. The tomb's golemforge powers up and grants us the ability to produce Forgotten Units. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">就让奥瑞厄斯消散在虚空之中吧。我们需要集中注意用神器的力量来净化这座埃斯特克墓穴。神器虽然失去了它的力量，但与支离破碎的至尊领主力量结合之后，巨大墓穴中剧毒的腐坏得到了净化，重新焕发出了生命精华所特有的蓝绿色光芒。墓穴中的魔像熔炉也恢复了运转，现在我们可以生产被遗忘者单位了。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Dvar Forge City</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">矮人锻造之城</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">An ancient Dvar Forge City where Dvarnos's Forge stood. His gauntlet is an artifact of legend, capable of leveling mountains and armies alike. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">迪瓦诺斯的熔炉坐落于这座古老的矮人锻造之城中。迪瓦诺斯的臂铠是一件传奇般的神器，可以夷平高山，铲除军队。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="70.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FIRST_RESULT_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We uncovered a tangle of pipes snaking in and out of the walls of the forge city. Scorch marks scar the walls. Charred encounter suits lie dormant and empty. Walkways spiral through the rings of concentric outer walls, leading to a massive fortress furnace chamber suspended above a pool of roiling magma.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们在锻造之城的城墙上发现了一些蜿蜒曲折的管道，墙上还留下了大火烧灼的痕迹，焦黑的防护服静静躺在那里，空空如也。过道盘旋着穿过同轴外墙的环廊，通向一个巨大的堡垒熔炉室，悬浮在一池翻滚的岩浆之上。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="96"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">A thick brass gate leans heavily to one side of the fortress forge. Many scorched cadavers litter on the floor just outside the gate. Most notably on the platform lies a gold-accented DV-R suit of what must have been a director. The gate bears the ironic inscription "Prosperity brings responsibility. Impatience brings ruin." </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">一扇厚厚的黄铜大门沉重地斜靠在堡垒锻炉的一侧，许多烧焦的尸体散落在门外的地板上。最引人注目的是台面上一件金碧辉煌的 DV-R 套服，这肯定是某位矮人领袖的装备。大门上刻着一行颇具讽刺意味的字：“繁荣带来责任，急躁带来毁灭。” </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">These scriptures mean nothing, so destroy the gate</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">这些铭文没有任何意义，摧毁大门</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="132.75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_RESULT_SUCCESS</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Expertly placed charges erupted in a chorus of booms. The massive brass gate seemed unmoved for just a moment, then slowly tilted and fell open with a creaking groan. We followed the chamber passage past a dozen proud bronze statues, each more grandiose than the prior. At the final statue, though, we paused. This one was missing its head.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">炸药在一阵巨大的齐鸣中爆炸，虽然这扇庞大的黄铜大门一开始没有什么动静，但不一会儿就吱吱地倾斜着打开了。我们沿着熔炉室的过道向里走去，经过了十几个威风凛凛的青铜雕像，一座比一座更显宏伟。不过，我们在最后一座雕像前停了下来，因为这座雕像的头不见了。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="108.75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_RESULT_FAILURE</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We've tried a dozen configurations on the gate, but with each barrage of explosives, the gate settled deeper into its place. Fire and concussive force echoed through the whole underground complex, rupturing pipes and spitting gouts of fire all about us. A final blast breaks a small hole in the gate. We were able to pry it apart, and clear the massive damage we did to the interior. After some effort, we start up mining production once again. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们一连对大门进行了十几轮爆破，然而每爆炸一次，大门就会陷得更深。火焰和震荡的冲击回荡在整个地下建筑群中，破坏了我们周围的管道，身旁迸射着火焰。最后一次爆炸终于在大门上炸开了一个小洞，我们撬开了大门，清除了门内杂乱的破坏。一番努力之后，我们再次开启了矿采作业。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Pay the gate's due</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">为大门献上祭品</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Paying the gate's due…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在为大门献上祭品…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="107.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We placed a large pile of Cosmite onto a loading platform, and the gate lifted up, swallowing our offering in the opening. The interior structure is immaculate, each hall lined with large brass statues depicting important figures of Dvar history. The last director statue is missing its head. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们把一大堆宇宙合金放在了装载台上，大门升了起来，吞掉了我们供奉的祭品。进入大门之后，我们发现建筑内部依然完好无损，每个大厅都排列着巨大的黄铜雕像，这些雕像都是矮人历史上的重要人物。但最后一座领袖雕像的头却不见了。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="120"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Just behind the strange statue, the room opened to a Dvar workshop. A massive statue of bolted iron presided over a court of anvils and forges. Molten steel flowed through composite ducts, glowing crimson hot. This place requires a DV-R suit. The statue at the door bore an inscription: "Only work pays for work. Only hardship produces perfection." It appeared to be another secret trial that craftsmen should understand. We think it requires that we sacrifice an item of quality craftsmanship...</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">就在这座奇怪的雕像后面，出现了一个通往矮人车间的房间。一尊巨型铁制雕像主持着这个由铁砧和锻炉组成的法庭。熔化的钢液流过复合管道，发出深红耀眼的光芒。看来需要一套 DV-R 防护服才能通过这里。门口的雕像上刻着一行字：“唯有以工才能换酬，唯有艰苦才能造就完美。”这似乎是工匠应当理解的另一个秘密试炼，我们认为这句话的意思是要我们供奉一件优质的手工制品…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Attempt to fool the arbitrator by using our current weapon</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">试着用我们目前的武器来欺骗仲裁者</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="75.75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT_SUCCESS</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We placed a worthless weapon clip onto the arbiter's hands, and the intricate workings of the device whirred to life. For a moment, we feared it might reject our "insulting" gift, but what does a statue know of value? Suddenly, the wall next to the statue opened. Pipes and plates retracted to reveal a fortified hallway. At the far end, a large vault door is sealed shut.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们把一把毫无价值的武器夹放在仲裁者的手中，复杂的设备开始运转起来。一时间，我们担心它可能会拒绝我们这份“侮辱性”的礼物，但难道一座雕像还能判断物品的价值？突然，雕像旁边的墙壁打开了，管道和墙板不断移动，露出了一条加固的走廊。在远处的另一端，一扇巨大的宝库门紧闭着。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="109.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT_FAILURE</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Thinking that no statue is smart enough to discern our deception, we placed a worthless weapon clip onto the arbiter's hands. There was a loud crack as the statue crushed the clip. The whole cavern began to rumble. The ceiling collapsed in places, crushing many good astro-archaeologists and one very mouthy mathematician. Magma rose from the cracks in the floor. The rest of us escaped with our lives. The fortress-forge sunk beneath the molten earth, leaving the facility only partly useful.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们认为没有雕像能聪明到识别出我们的骗术，因此把一把毫无价值的武器夹放在了仲裁者的手中。然而，雕像压碎了武器夹，发出了一声巨响，整个洞穴也开始隆隆作响。天花板塌了下来，把许多优秀的天文考古学家和一位口齿伶俐的数学家碾成了碎片。岩浆从地板的裂缝中涌出，剩下没被压扁的人四散而逃。堡垒熔炉室沉入了熔土之中，只留下了一座快要散架的设施。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Forge a weapon to prove our worth</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">锻造武器来证明我们的价值</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Forging a weapon to prove our worth….</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在锻造武器证明我们的价值….</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="108.75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Our craftsmen may not be expert Dvar, but they found the tools and machinery of such fine quality that even simplest items they created were of the highest grade. Using refined Cosmite, they crafted a weapon of impressive power. After placing it onto the arbiter's hands, the statue whirred to life. The wall next to the statue transformed into a hidden vault door. We retrieved the weapon and headed towards the door. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的工匠可能不是矮人专家，但他们找到了精良的工具和机械。有了这些工具，就算是制造一些最简单的东西也都具有极高的品质。我们的工匠使用精炼的宇宙合金制造出了一把威力惊人的武器。我们将武器放在了仲裁者的手中，雕像便随即运转了起来。不久之后，雕像旁边的墙面上露出了一个隐藏的宝库门。我们取回了武器，向门口走去。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Forge armor to prove our worth</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">锻造护甲来证明我们的价值…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Forging armor to prove our worth….</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在锻造护甲证明我们的价值…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="98.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">Our craftsmen get to work using the fine Dvar tools. Though they've never used them, the tools are of such fine quality that they could not help but create a masterwork of armor. Once the final touches were applied, the armor was placed upon the arbiter statue's hands, and a loud crank wheel rolled away the pipes and levers to reveal a hidden passage behind the statue. At the end of it was a sealed vault door. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的工匠着手用精良的矮人工具制造护甲。虽然他们从未使用过这些工具，但工具本身的质量使他们制造出了一件大师级的护甲。在完成了最后的润色工作之后，我们将护甲放入了仲裁者雕像的手中。一个巨大的曲柄轴轮卷走了管道，露出了雕像背后隐藏的通道，而在通道的尽头是一扇紧闭着的宝库大门。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_4_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Let our Forgemasters work their craft in the venerable forge</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">让我们的铸造大师在这庄严的熔炉中发挥才能</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="30"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_4_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Our Forgemasters are working their craft…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的铸造大师正在制造物品…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="108.75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_4_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The Forgemasters are in awe at the quality of tools in this impressive facility. Finely-crafted Cosmite items become precious relics at their hands. We were meant to work with these tools, and each one filled a deep-ringing purpose within us. Reluctantly, we placed our crafted items onto the arbiter statue's hands. There was a shifting and cranking of pipes, and behind us, we saw a passage to a vault door.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们的铸造大师对这所神圣设施里的工具报以极高的敬畏。精心制作的宇宙合金物品经过他们的炮制成为了珍贵的圣物。我们注定要使用这些工具，并且每个人的心中都充满了一种深刻的使命感。我们十分不情愿地把那件精心制作的物品放到了仲裁者雕像的手中。突然，管道开始移动，我们身后出现了一条通往宝库大门的道路。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="105.75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_START</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">As we approached, the vault opened. Molten steel cascaded down the walls. This was not itself the forge, at least not originally, but our researchers thought it serves the same purpose as the massive heatsinks found on Dvar deep-earth drills. At the center of the large chamber rested a fortified container, a gauntlet glimmering within it that was not unlike that of a Dvar Foreman. But it shone with a beauty unheard of in Dvar craftsmanship. Someone murmured, "The legendary Gauntlet of Empires!"</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当我们靠近时，宝库大门打开了。液化钢铁从墙壁上倾泻而下。这里本来并不是一个熔炉，至少最初不是，但我们的研究员认为它与矮人钻土机上的巨大散热器作用相同。在这个巨大房间的中央，放着一个坚固的容器，里面有一副闪着微光的臂铠。这副臂铠跟矮人工头的臂铠并无二样，但它却闪耀着一种矮人工艺中从未见过的美丽。这时，不知是谁低声说了一句：“传说中的帝国臂铠！”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="55.5"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s65"><Data ss:Type="String">Claim the gauntlet</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">拿走臂铠</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="62.25"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">We approach the ornate gauntlet. The vault door slams shut behind us. Large hydraulic doors pull open, revealing high-caliber mounted turrets. The Dvar statues suddenly animate and train their weapons upon us.  </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当我们接近这副华丽的臂铠时，宝库的大门突然砰地一声关上了。大型液压门打开，露出了数座大口径炮台。矮人雕像也突然像是获得了生命，将武器对准了我们。  </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="45.75"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The Dvar trap of weapons and deadly animatronic statues are ready to riddle us all with pain. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">矮人的陷阱武器和致命的机械雕像准备铲除我们。 </Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="96"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">THE_DVAR_FORGE_CITY</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell ss:StyleID="s64"><Data ss:Type="String">The final defenses fell before us. A voice crackled through a hidden speaker, "You have done well, unlike Director Ragnar. You have proven a dedication to creation and craft. My gauntlet is yours to take; wield it well. Destruction comes easier than creation. Balance it wisely." The case slid open with a depressurizing hiss, and the Gauntlet of Empires is now ours!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">随着最后一道防御的倒塌，一个声音从隐蔽的扬声器里传来：“你做得很好，不像领袖拉格纳尔。你已证明了自己对创造和工艺的奉献，拿走我的臂铠吧，好好使用它的力量。但要记住，毁灭比创造更容易。明智地平衡两者的关系。”随着一声压力放空的嘶嘶声，箱子滑了开来。帝国臂铠现在是我们的了！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="8" ss:StyleID="s63"/></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Forgotten must be able to unlock this gate</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">被遗忘者肯定能够打开这扇门</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">The Forgotten is an in-game NPC faction</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Forgotten approach and raising a glowing rod to infuse the device with the flow of essence. As the rod dimmed, the device activated and the tomb entrance swung open, revealing a chamber within. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">被遗忘者走近并举起了一根发光棒，将精华流注入了设备之中。随着发光棒逐渐变暗，设备也慢慢激活了，里面的一个房间显露了出来。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Sanctum of Awakening</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">觉醒圣殿</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Es'Teq Crypt, buried below the sands of Obolus-5. Its imposing architecture leaves no doubt that this is where the legacy of the Es'Teq is still hidden.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">埃斯特克地穴被埋葬在奥博罗斯 5 号星的沙土之下，这蔚为壮观的建筑毫无疑问就是埃斯特克的遗产仍然隐藏的地方。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Regenesis Ark is a device mentioned in the campaign</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FIRST_RESULT_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We expected to find beauty on this world, but Hatyl Es’Ran's descriptions could not do this place justice. The Sanctorum stands monolithic in the cavern that shielded it for centuries; a miracle it has never been discovered.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们期望发现这个世界的美好，但哈泰尔·埃斯兰的描述却无法形容这个地方的美丽。这座圣所坐落在一个巨大的洞穴里，几个世纪以来一直未被发现，这里是一个世人从未目睹过的奇迹。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Hatyl Es'Ran is a male Kir'Ko character</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Sadly, our joy is interrupted by a sensor reading. RPRs were ghosting our exploration sensors, and we've identified their tell-tale destructive marks on the exterior seal of the Sanctorum. Unable to reach the inner parts of the complex, they are marking us as their new extermination targets.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">遗憾的是，我们的快乐被传感器的读数打断了。RPR 跟随我们的探索传感器而来，我们在圣所的外部封口处也发现了它们留下的破坏性痕迹。由于无法到达建筑群的内部，它们把我们标记为了新的消灭目标。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">RPR or Reapers are an-game mechanical unit type</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Assault the RPRs</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">袭击 RPR</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The RPRs know we've discovered their presence and have enough tactical sense not to fight both us and the Es'Teq they seek to annihilate. We have this chance to destroy them. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">RPR 知道我们已经发现了它们，但它们也有足够的战术意识，不会与我们和埃斯特克的灵魂同时交战。我们得抓住这个机会毁掉这些 RPR。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The RPRs are programmed to prevent any and all of the Es'Teq from escaping, including artifacts, so they will destroy us if we come closer to the Sanctorum.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">RPR 的编程设计不会放过任何一个埃斯特克，包括埃斯特克的神器。因此如果我们离圣所太近，它们将摧毁我们。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We cut the RPRs down. Good riddance to a terrible idea stuck in the past. The war that lead to their creation ended ages ago. These are relics best left decommissioned. So, we've done our duty to the universe today by destroying them.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们打败了 RPR，摆脱了陷在过去的可怕想法。导致它们诞生的那场战争早在很久之前就已经结束了，这些遗物最好留在这里被所有人遗忘。因此，摧毁它们是我们对整个宇宙履行的职责。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Attempt to distract the RPRs with an Essence filled crystal</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">试着用充满水晶的精华转移 RPR 的注意力</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Attempting to distract the RPRs with an Essence filled crystal…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在用充满水晶的精华转移 RPR 的注意力…</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_RESULT_SUCCESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We transferred some Essence into a crystal and tossed it down a ravine. The RPRs swiftly locked on, assuming it to be a Heritor attempting to flee. While they were in pursuit, we slipped into the unattended Sanctorum entrance.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们把一些精华转化成了水晶，然后把水晶扔进了一个峡谷之中。RPR 迅速锁定了精华，认为这是一名企图逃跑的继承者。趁着 RPR 追赶精华之际，我们溜进了无人看管的圣所。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_RESULT_FAILURE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We attempted to distract the RPRs with an essence crystal, but the crystal shattered at the bottom of the ravine, enraging the RPRs and making them all the more determined to cut us to ribbons. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们试图用一个精华水晶来分散 RPR 的注意力，但水晶在峡谷底部摔碎了。RPR 对此非常生气，它们现在更想要把我们切成碎片了。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ask Jack Gelder and his troops to intervene</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">请求杰克·格尔德和他的部队介入此事</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Jack Gelder is a male Vanguard character</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Keeping his earlier promise, Jack Gelder didn't hesitate to send in his Purifiers to our aid. Their PyrX fires made quick work of the Reapers, clearing the path for our further advance.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">杰克·格尔德遵守了他先前的诺言，毫不犹豫地派遣了他的净化者前来帮助我们。派尔克斯的火焰很快解决了这些死神，为我们清理出了一条继续前进的路。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Egalitarian League of Planets, or ELOP, is a unification of rules, like the UN</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The inner sanctum is gated. Upon the emerald structure is an inscription that reads, "All must contribute an equal share." We believe it is either a warning that if we enter we will die, or that we should pay a tithe of Essence to be admitted beyond the point of the gate.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">圣所内部被一扇大门保护着，翡翠的建筑上刻有一句话，写着：“所有人都必须贡献一份平等的力量。”我们认为，这要么是在警告我们如果进入就会丢掉性命，要么就是在暗示我们应该奉上一些精华才能获准进入大门。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Set up a temporary phase portal and attempt to bypass the gate entirely</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">设置一个临时的相位传送门，尝试绕过大门</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Setting up a temporary phase portal to attempt to bypass the gate entirely…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在设置临时相位传送门来尝试绕过大门…</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT_SUCCESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Using the science of VoidTech, we bypassed the gate altogether, moving matter into an alternate phase and passing through the gate as though it wasn't even there. Once again, VoidTech scientists prove that their scientific principles have outgrown the quaint concepts of solid matter and typical space-time.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们利用虚空科技完全绕过了这扇大门，把物质转移到了另一个位面，然后穿了过去，就好像大门根本不存在一样。虚空科技的科学家们再一次证明，他们的科学原理已经超越了固态物质和典型时空这样固有的概念。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT_FAILURE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The phase portal should have worked, since all sensible people recognize the superiority of VoidTech science, but an interaction with the Es'Teq device must have created a matter resonance field that caused it all to explode. Nobody died, but we've all had better days. Even so, the tithe doesn't need to be paid, because we blasted a hole clean through the gate.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">相位传送门本应是一种可行的方法，因为所有人都见识过虚空科技的优越。然而，相位传送门与埃斯特克设备的交互产生了一个物质共振力场，导致发生了爆炸。虽然并没有人员伤亡，但这样的事情还是不发生最好。不过，我们也因此无须献上任何东西，因为我们在大门上面炸开了一个窟窿。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Es'Ran is an Es'Teq Precursor, so he will know the proper rites</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">埃斯兰是埃斯特克的预兆者，他肯定知道相应的仪式</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hatyl Es'Ran is performing his rites…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">哈泰尔·埃斯兰正在执行仪式…</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hatyl Es'Ran placed his hand upon the gate, and chanted a rhythmic melody. Then he made us each hold a part of the gate. There was a warm feeling, as though we were sharing a part of our deepest feelings with the structure itself. Without even being coached, we all started what can best be described as singing. Then the gate glowed bright and opened to us. Instead of feeling drained, we feel invigorated!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">哈泰尔·埃斯兰把手放在大门上，吟诵了一段有节奏的旋律，然后他让我们每人都摸着大门的一部分。随后，一股温暖的感觉充满了全身，好像我们在和这建筑本身分享内心深处的部分情感一样。我们站在那里，口中竟然吟唱起一首从未听过的歌曲。接着，大门闪着亮光打开了。我们本以为经过这一切后会感觉浑身疲惫，但我们却充满了活力！</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pay the tithe</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">献上贡品</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We entered a chamber glowing with life. Pools of clean water teemed with jewels of Essence, which flows there like a wellspring. In the center, we see an obsidian Ark flanked by two Forgotten constructs. Es'Ran said that the guardians are the "Hands of Artok". One is called "The Hand that Gives" and the other "The Hand that Takes". They did not recognize us and prepared to attack. Es'Ran held out a hand, but they did not respond. Something was wrong.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们走进了一个充满生机的房间，清澈的水池里充满了精华宝石像泉水一样流淌。房间的中央有一个黑曜石方舟，两侧环绕着两个被遗忘者的造物。埃斯兰说，它们是名为“阿尔托克双臂”的守护者，其中一个是“应予之手”，另一个则是“索取之手”。然而，它们没有认出我们并准备向我们发起进攻。埃斯兰伸出了一只手，却没有得到任何回应。这里有什么地方不对劲。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Face the Guardians</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">直面守护者</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Hands of Artok hum with immense power. They look ready to crush us, but hold--perhaps in deference to Es'Ran--for us to make the first move. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">阿尔托克的双臂发出巨大的力量，看起来像是要压扁我们，但它们并没有立即行动，而是定在那里等待我们率先行动，也许是因为埃斯兰的原因。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Ark in the center of the chamber is shimmering with undeniable beauty. However, the Hands of Artok are still blocking our path to it.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">房间中央的方舟闪烁着无法否认的美丽，但阿尔托克的双臂依然阻挡着我们前往方舟的道路。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We laid low the Hands of Artok and approached the Ark. The platform ascended as the apex of the Sanctorum shook and cracked to behold a field of stars. Exposed to the night sky, the Ark is resting there, waiting for us to crack its last seal.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们击败了阿尔托克的双臂，向方舟走去。平台逐渐上升，圣所的顶端开始摇晃并出现了裂隙，我们甚至看见了一片星空。方舟停在夜空之下，等待我们揭开它最后的封印。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Contact the Forgotten about the uncorrupted guardians</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">联系被遗忘者，了解未堕落的守护者</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Contacting the Forgotten about the uncorrupted guardians…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在联系被遗忘者，了解未堕落的守护者…</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Es'Ran hesitates to contact the Forgotten. They are corrupted Heritors, focused on revenge, but they share an origin. We figure they could help control the Hands of Artok. At first, we think they came just to feed upon the essence here, but once within the Sanctorum's heart, the red ire of Forgotten suffering changed. Something in this place purified them. The Hands of Artok and the Forgotten embrace each other. We are free to activate the Ark.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">埃斯兰犹豫着要不要联系被遗忘者，因为他们是一心只想要复仇的堕落继承者，但和埃斯兰却有着共同的起源。我们认为这些被遗忘者可以帮忙控制住阿尔托克的双臂。起初，我们认为被遗忘者来到这里只是为了汲取这里的精华，但他们一进入圣所的中心，他们痛苦的怒火就发生了改变。这个地方有什么东西净化了他们。阿尔托克的双臂与被遗忘者互相接受了对方，我们也可以没有阻碍地激活方舟了。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Regenesis Ark pulses at the heart of the Sanctorum. The Hands of Artok, ancient guardians of the Ark, watch over it, preventing us from claiming the artifact. Meanwhile, the Forgotten await our signal to assist in our assault. They are hoping to gain acces to the two exalted guardians.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">再生方舟在圣所中心跳动着，古老的方舟守护者阿尔托克的双臂阻挡着我们拿走神器的道路。与此同时，被遗忘者等待着我们的信号准备协助进攻，他们想要接近这两个高尚的守护者。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The platform ascended, lifting the Ark of Regenesis up to the ceiling. The whole top of the Sanctorum's pyramid unfolded like a flower in bloom, unveiling the stars before our eyes, tears streaming down our faces. The Forgotten glowed in silent awe at their progenitors, watching and waiting. We felt the Ark pulsate, and as if in chorus, the stars blinked back at us with the same fervent throbbing. Something greater than us all has awakened in the universe this day. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">平台向上升去，将再生方舟抬至了天花板上。这个金字塔一般的圣所顶部就像盛开的鲜花一样绽放开来，露出了满天的繁星。看到这一景象，我们不禁留下了泪水。被遗忘者对他们的祖先肃然起敬，注视，等待。我们感到方舟也在颤动，仿佛加入了我们的合唱，群星也在炽热地闪动回应着我们。今天，比我们更伟大的东西在宇宙中觉醒了。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NAME</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">House of Emperors</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝皇之殿</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DESCRIPTION</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A massive temple complex built around the world's government palace, a great cult lives here. Thriving, regardless of species, united under their worship of the emperors as deities. The cult features several sects attempting to rebuild the emperors in their own way.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">世界政府宫殿的周围建造了一座巨大的神庙，里面住着一群教徒。他们不分种族，不断在这里发展壮大，敬奉着被他们奉为神明的帝皇，在这种虔诚的崇拜中团结一致。这些教徒分成了好几种教派，每个教派都想要以自己的方式重建帝皇。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FIRST_RESULT_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We unearthed a government palace complex. Star Union banners lined the walls. Small statues representing all the known emperors and empresses of the Union filled the rooms. Judging from the artifacts we've unearthed thus far, there must have been a terrible siege here, and sometime afterwards the whole place became a shrine complete with scented cred-sticks for burning offerings to various historical figures. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们发掘出了一个政府宫殿，宫殿墙上排列着星际联盟的旗帜，房间里摆满了各种小雕像，各自代表着有名的联盟帝皇和女皇。从我们目前挖掘出来的神器来看，这里一定遭到了某种可怕的围攻。不久之后，整个地方就变成了一座神殿，里面放满了香烛，用来祭拜各种历史人物。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In the spacious halls of the palace sat a construct shaped like a man, bearing a lifelike face. Shadows drifted around the room, seemingly stalking the figure as one of our historians explained that the man-bot was constructed to be a likeness of Emperor Lennick Tennebres. He appeared to be in agony. Are there creatures lurking in the shadows of this room as well? We all felt an uneasy agitation as we consider what to do.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">宫殿宽敞的大厅里坐着一个人形建筑，他的脸型非常逼真。我们的一位历史学家解释说这个人型机器人是照着帝皇莱尼科·特勒布瑞斯的样子建造的。这时我们发现房间里有阴影在四处飘动，似乎在追随这个人型机器人。他看起来好像很痛苦，难道这些暗影中潜伏着什么生物？我们感到一阵不安，思考着接下来的行动。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Lennick Tennebres is a historic male figure</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">He must need help; destroy these shadow monsters!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">他一定需要帮助；消灭这些暗影怪物！</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We step forth, weapons at the ready to engage the shadow monsters. They swarm behind Tennebres. He rises, eyes filled with black mist. He may not be on our side, and may resist being rescued!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们走上前，准备好武器对付那些暗影怪物。但它们成群结队地跟在特勒布瑞斯的身后，特勒布瑞斯站了起来，眼里蒙上了一层黑雾。他也许并非善类，也不需要我们拯救！</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A shadow-possessed Emperor Tennebres paces around the main hall, surrounded by creatures of darkness. We should probably just destroy them all.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">被阴影附身的特勒布瑞斯帝皇在大厅里踱步，周围环绕着黑暗的生物。或许，我们应该把他们一起消灭。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">With the last of the shadows purged, the Emperor Tennebres construct collapsed on the floor. His last words in his final moments were exhaled and barely audible. "Thank... you..." He reached up and handed us his insignia. "Take it. Free... the... others..." Others? We are left pondering what other constructs are being tormented by the shades of this strange complex. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们清除了最后的暗影，帝皇特勒布瑞斯的构造物也随之倒塌在了地板上。他在死前艰难地说出了最后的遗言，小声得我们几乎快要听不见了：“谢…谢你们…”他伸出手递给我们他的徽章，“拿着。解…解救…其他人…”其他人？我们不禁开始思考，难道这里还有其他构造物被这个奇怪建筑中的暗影所折磨？ </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Leave the man to the shadows</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">让他留在暗影中吧</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We've left Tennebres to remain in the shadows. Nothing good comes from meddling with a dreaming man. Though his presence was unsettling, it leaves us to wonder just how authentic the Emperor's simulacrum really was to the long dead version. Perhaps this place will yield further answers as we continue on our journey.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们将特勒布瑞斯留在了阴影之中，毕竟干预梦境中的人不会有什么好下场。尽管他的存在令人不安，但我们不禁好奇，这样的拟像到底和早已死去的帝皇有多相似？也许在我们接下来的旅途中，这个地方会给出更多的答案。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Celestian teachings may calm this troubled man's mind…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">也许星神的教导能够让这个身陷囹圄的人平静下来…</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Celestian is an-game religious secret tech</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Calming the troubled man's mind with Celestian teachings…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在用星神的教导让这个身陷囹圄的人平静下来…</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_2_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Celestians can disperse shadows quite handily, so we set about calling upon our inner light. Letting our minds connect, we drew out the young Tennebres kept within his mind, but he recoiled. Descending deeper, his mind unfurled into a blackened wasteland. We reached out and grasped at his true conciousness. Upon guiding him gently away from the darkness, the construct's face filled with surprise. As it passed it whispered "Thank you...".</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">星神可以轻而易举地驱散暗影，所以我们开始召唤内心的光明。我们将思想与年轻的特勒布瑞斯连接起来，但他并没有回应。他的思绪越来越模糊，逐渐沉入了一片暗黑的废土之中。我们伸出手抓住了他真正的意识，慢慢引导他远离了黑暗。这个构造物的脸上充满了惊喜，他清醒后低声说道：“谢谢…”。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We discovered another artificial emperor in a palace armory. He was a hulking figure, dressed in only a loincloth. His skin glistened black as that of Khansu, the Burning Emperor, his choice of dress a sign of defiance. In life, he despised the wealth of his station, calling it decadence. He burned worlds for the downtrodden and underprivileged. He knew tragedy. Many historians supposed he lost his mind to madness before his own homeworld was destroyed.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们在宫殿的一个武器库中发现了另一个人造帝皇，他巨大的身躯上只裹着一条缠腰布，皮肤黑得发亮。燃烧帝王坎苏如此的装束象征着他反抗的精神，在这位帝皇的一生中，他鄙视地位给他带来的财富，并将其称之为堕落。他为备受压迫的人民和弱势群体烧毁了这个世界。他知道什么才是悲剧。许多历史学家认为，这名帝皇在自己的家园被摧毁之前就已经疯了。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Khansu is an ancient male emperor. The Burning Emperor is his title because he lit a world on fire with him still in it to defeat that world's CORE AI</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">This man was a monster, and his memory should be dealt with as such</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">这个男人是个怪物，他的记忆也应该被处理掉</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The false Khansu watches as we approach, our weapons ready. The Burning Emperor's expression twists into a scornful glare. Indignation rises in his voice, "You would assault your Emperor?" He snaps his fingers and a mob of plasmoids skitter into the room. The air warps in the heat. We are trapped in his flaming rage.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们准备好了武器，一步步接近这个虚假的坎苏帝皇。燃烧帝皇的表情扭曲成了一种轻蔑的怒视，他的声音里充满了愤怒：“你们要攻击自己的帝皇？”他打个响指，一群等离子粒团飞入了房间。空气在高温中扭曲，我们被困在了他燃烧的怒火之中。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The palace's armory is wreathed with fire, plasmoids skittering around the silhouette of The Burning Emperor. They must be dealt with if we are to be able to make any more progress.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">火焰包围了宫殿的武器库，等离子粒团在燃烧帝皇的周围飞舞。如果要想取得任何进展，我们必须先解决掉他们。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Khansu fell to our assault. Looking up, he cried out, "I know I was never him, but his memories are mine. The good he did could not erase the tragedy he caused. I see that. I see their faces burning. I see it all." He toppled over, life leaving his body. This might have been but an imposter, but it was an echo of what once lived, and we are left to ponder the dark past of the Star Union. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">坎苏在我们的攻击中倒下了。他抬起头大声地叫喊：“我其实一直知道我永远也不可能成为他，但他的记忆存在于我的体内，他所做的善事无法抹去他造成的悲剧。我看到了，我看到了他们的脸在燃烧，我全都看到了。”说完，他就倒了下去。他虽然只是坎苏的冒充者，但他也曾经是存在于世的回声，这使我们不禁开始沉思星际联盟黑暗的过去。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Emperor Khansu, our forefathers speak fondly of your reign. Will you grant us your boon?</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝皇坎苏，我们的祖先对你的统治赞不绝口。你会给予我们恩惠吗？</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Spoken by the Dvar</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Emperor Khansu's expression changed to recognition, his eyes taking on the look of an endearing father. He spoke, "In the miners, I saw something of my home before it became my pyre, flourishing in the fires of industry." His enthusiasm slackened as he continued, " I understand I am not who you think I am, young one, but I bear Khansu's memories. Know that Khansu would have been proud to see what your people have become." </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝皇坎苏的表情变成了一种认可，眼神中带有父亲般的慈爱，说道：“在矿工身上，我看到了我的家乡变成灰烬之前的影子，它在工业的火焰中不断繁荣。”他一边说着，一边却失去了之前的热情，“但我明白，我并不是你想象中的那个人，年轻人，我只是承载着坎苏的记忆而已。如果坎苏能够看见你们如今的样貌，他一定会感到自豪的。” </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bow to Emperor Khansu, grandfather of the Promethean!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">向圣火使者的先祖帝皇坎苏臣服！</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">Spoken by the Promethean</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Emperor's simulacrum grinned from ear to ear. He spoke of divinity and the fires that were started to end all worlds. He proclaimed our leader a herald of rebirth, granting him the title of Sol Paramount. Though this may only be an artificial approximation of the Burning Lord, his proclamations inspire our troops. They glow like healthy embers at his endorsement.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">帝皇逆像露出了满面的笑容，他谈到神性和那场毁灭了所有星球的大火。帝皇宣布我们的领袖为重生的先驱，并授予了他“太阳神统治者”的头衔。虽然这可能只是一个燃烧领主的人造复制品，但他的宣言仍然激励了我们的部队。在他的支持下，我们的部队就像旺盛的火苗一样充满精力。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">As we ascended the complex's main spire, we entered a vaulted chamber lined with cryopods. Each pod was charged and held a life in stasis. Standing in the room's center as if he stepped from a page of history was the Emperor Tholian. His charismatic smile and icy eyes pierced us. He was blocking the only way out of this room: a spiral staircase. "The Architect is not receiving visitors." it's damaged voice shrieked.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们登上这座建筑的主塔后进入了一个拱形的房间，里面排列摆放着许多冷冻舱。每个冷冻舱都接通着电源，维系着舱内沉睡的生命。帝皇托利安站在房间中央，仿佛是从历史中走出来的一样。他露出迷人的微笑，冰冷的眼神刺透了我们的心灵。他挡住了这个房间的唯一出口：一个螺旋楼梯。“建造师不接见访客。”他用嘶哑的嗓音尖声说道。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We must free these people; destroy the abomination</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们必须解放这些人；摧毁这个令人厌恶的家伙</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We approach the doppelganger. In the voice of the Tholian, it warns us, "The Architect is not expecting visitors. But perhaps your parts can be of use to him." Tholian draws his weapon and charges us in a very undignified fury.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">当我们接近这个帝皇的复制品时，他用托利安的声音向我们发出警告：“建造师没有想到会有访客到来，但你们的残肢对他而言也许能够派上用场。”托利安拔出了他的武器，怒气冲冲地对我们发起了攻击。</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">The Architect is male</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Access to the central control chamber is blocked by a mad Emperor Tholian intent on destroying us for some weird agenda that only the insane might guess.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">发狂的帝皇托利安封锁了通往中央控制室的通道。他想要摧毁我们，至于理由，也许只有疯子才能猜得到。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tholian's double collapsed as we finished our assault. With his last breath, he called out, "I may look like him, but I was not trained by the actual Emperor. He knew CORE would require it of him, and saw to it that there was very little left of his mind for the Union's benefit." We turned our attention to the cryopods, freeing the disturbed victims from their frozen stasis. The thawed people form a caravan willing to join our side. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">托利安的复制品倒在了我们的攻击之下。他含着最后一口气，喊道：“我可能长得像他，但我并不是真正的帝皇。他知道'核心'对他的要求，他也注意到了自己对星际联盟利益的思想已经所剩无几了。”我们把注意力转向了冷冻舱，把那些不安的受害者从冻僵的休眠中解救了出来。解冻后的人们组成一支商队，愿意加入我们的阵营。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Lie that their logs must be incomplete, and that the Architect requested us himself</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">撒谎说他们的记录日志一定并不完整，是建造师亲自要求我们到这里来的</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_RESULT_SUCCESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">"So I see... I am aware of my... limitations... I am missing my personality... I must have missed this too... You may pass." He slumped dejectedly to the side, strangely unlike an Emperor in demeanor, and freely surrendered access to the next chamber.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“我明白了…我意识到了自己的…局限…我想念我的人格…我一定也失去了它…你们可以通过了。”他沮丧地倒在了一旁。奇怪的是，他的举止并不像是一个帝皇，并且还自愿打开了通往下一个房间的道路。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">"I may be imperfect, but I understand my master's wishes, and you were not a part of them. Though perhaps he can use your... parts..." The oddly disingenuous Tholian then activates a dozen constructs that swarm the room as he readies his weapon. He clearly didn't buy our lie.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">“我也许并不完美，但我理解主人的愿望，而你们并不在他的愿望之内。不过，也许他还是能够利用你们的…身体…”接着，这个古怪而狡猾的托利安激活了十几个构造物挤满了整个房间，与此同时他也拿起了武器。显然，他并没有相信我们的谎言。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Access to the central control spire is blocked by this mad-emperor and his weapon-bots. He guards the cryopods too.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">这名疯狂的帝皇和他的武器机器人封锁了进入中央控制塔的道路。不仅如此，他还守着那些冷冻舱。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_RESULT_FAILURE</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The mockery of Tholian crumpled to the ground, and with his last breath, he cries out, "Incomplete! If I had his knowledge, I could defeat you! But he robbed us all of his mind!" Then with dramatic seizures, he claws the air and cackles out loud. The pods are damaged and of no use to us anymore. </Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">托利安的嘲弄逐渐消失了，他用最后一口气喊道：“不完整！如果我有他的知识，我就能打败你！但他夺走了我们全部的思想！”接着，随着一阵剧烈的痉挛，他挥手抓着空气大笑起来。冷冻舱已经全部损毁，对我们不再有用了。 </Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_3_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Destroy the abomination and siphon the pods' essence - their time passed long ago</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">摧毁这个可憎之物，吸取冷冻舱的精华，他们的时代早已逝去了</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_3_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We approach the creature wearing Tholian's face as it warns us, "The Architect is not expecting visitors. Perhaps you can give yourselves to him, the way I did not. Perhaps your minds will be intact enough to be copied. Mine was not. Mine was not. Mine was not!" His arms twitch violently and he draws his weapons with which to destroy us.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们走近这个和托利安长得一模一样的生物，他发出警告：“建造师不希望见到访客。或许你们可以像我一样，把自己献给他。也许你们的思想能够被完整地复制下来，但我的却没有。我的思想不完整，我的思想不完整！”他的手臂猛烈地抽动着，拔出了武器想要消灭我们。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_3_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fake Emperor Tholian is armed and guards access to the control chamber stairwell, but when we attempted to siphon the cryopods, he trained his weapons on us and fired a warning shot. We must obliterate this obstacle.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">假帝皇托利安全副武装，守卫着通往控制室的通道。当我们试图汲取冷冻舱的精华时，他将武器对准了我们并开了一枪表示警告。我们必须扫除这个障碍。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tholian's lifeless corpse lies splayed across the floor. We ignored his last words. The pods are ours now. Each one is being transformed into a historical celebrity. Our Siphoners attached Es'Teq probes to them. Soon, the imposters of the past are transformed into brightly glowing turquoise essence. Strangely, the amount of essence in our stores is nearly twice that of what we would anticipate from draining this number of victims, almost as if they each had second lifeforce within them...</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">托利安毫无生气的尸体横倒在地板上，我们无视了他的遗言。这些冷冻舱现在是我们的了，里面的每个人都正在转变成某个历史上的名人。我们的生命汲取者将埃斯特克的探针连接在了冷冻舱上，不一会，这些代表着过去的冒牌货就被转化成了绿松石一般明亮的精华。奇怪的是，我们获得的精华几乎是预期中的两倍。这些受害者的数量并没有那么多，但从我们获得的精华来看，就好像他们每个人的体内都还有一种生命力存在似的…</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_START</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In the Consul's spire, we found a workshop. Bodies littered the room, each wearing a face of historical significance. An unfinished simulacrum sat at the room's center. Its face was that of Emperor Mora. An old human was tinkering with a device attached to his arm. His tottering voice called out, "I found their minds, so many minds. CORE used them. I copied them. They said I was mad, but I can bring them back! Who are you foil an old man's dream?"</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们在领事尖塔中发现了一个车间。房间里散落着许多尸体，每具尸体都长着一张具有历史意义的面孔。房间中央竖立着一个未完成的拟像，它的面部是帝皇莫拉的模样。一位老人正在摆弄他手臂上的设备，他用颤抖的声音喊道：“我找到了他们的思想，那么多的思想。‘核心’利用了他们，而我则复制了他们。其他人都说我疯了，但我能给他们带来重生！你们凭什么阻止一位老人的梦想？”</Data></Cell><Cell ss:Index="7"><Data ss:Type="String">The Consul is a location in this site</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_1_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">These creations disturb those who should be put to rest.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">这些造物打扰了那些本应得到安息之人。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_1_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Architect laughs, getting to his feet. He is amused. "Is that so? Ignorance. That's the foolish nonsense these told me." He points to the bodies. "It is time I show you the only way out." The man's expression turns grim, he snaps his fingers, and the unfinished works littering the room stir to life! His latest creation comes to his side. The Architect's form changes--more menacing--as a massive abyssal creature materializes behind him!</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">建造师感觉到好笑，他站了起来说：“真的是这样么？无知。这是他们告诉我的那些蠢话。”他指着那些尸体说道，“是时候告诉你们唯一的出路了。”他的表情变得严肃起来，打了一个响指，整个屋子里未完成的作品全都活了过来！他最新的作品也来到了他的身边。当一个庞大的深渊生物具化并出现在了他的身后时，建造师的形态变得更加险恶了！</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_1_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In the government palace's spire lies a workshop where the Architect of these artificial emperors loiters with his abyssal allies. He must be taken care of.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">在政府宫殿的尖塔上有一个车间，这些人造帝皇的建造师和他的深渊盟友在这里游荡。必须解决掉他。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_1_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Architect has been destroyed. His body was more machine than man. It was not even clear whether his mind was his own. We have no idea how old this being was, but there is plenty here to learn from.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">建造师被消灭了。他的身体与其说是人类，倒不如说更像是一个机器。我们甚至不知道他的思想是否还是他自己的思想。我们不知道这里存在了多久，但这里有很多我们值得学习的东西。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_2_TEXT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Your work can serve the Union's rebirth... if you join us</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">你的工作可以帮助联盟复兴…如果你加入我们的话</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_5_CHOICE_2_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The ancient Architect laughs. "Enlightened. Finally, one who understands. They said I was mad, but now the world is mad. Yes. Yes. The minds I've copied will benefit your empire. Imagine it, a whole cadre of emperors at your command. Yes. All those minds." A disturbing glint reflects in his drifting eyes. "Yes. I will give my arts. We will create masterworks! You will see... the art comes first."</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">这名古老的建造师笑了起来，说：“太好了。终于有人能够理解我了。他们都说我疯了，但现在是这个世界疯了。没错。没错！我复制的思想将造福于你的帝国。想象一下吧，一大群帝皇听候你的支配。是的，所有的帝皇都将听命于你。”他飘忽不定的眼里闪过一丝令人不安的神色。“好。我愿意献出我的艺术品。我们将共创杰作！你将会发现…艺术才是最重要的。”</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SANCTUM_OF_AWAKENING</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_3_CHOICE_3_RESULT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We each touched the gate as instructed, and sure enough, we felt weaker: the gate drained our Essence. Little by little, we saw the structure pulse with life, and the gate opened. We are weaker but we have passed another obstacle.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">我们每个人都按照指示触碰了大门。果然，我们感觉变得更加虚弱了，大门抽走了我们的精华。慢慢地，我们看到这个建筑具有了生命般的律动，随后大门便打开了。虽然我们变得更加虚弱，但至少我们又越过了一道障碍。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">HOUSE_OF_EMPERORS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_3_IN_PROGRESS</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Attacking the abomination…</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">正在攻击虚假的托利安帝皇…</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_START_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The golems in the center of the tomb served to ward the heart from intruders. They suddenly awakened and descended from their plinths to consume any who dared enter the area. Using what we learned from the golemforge, our engineers managed to dismantle the golems' mobility actuators, leaving them clawing helplessly on the ground. Now that they are disabled, we can now approach the High Lord.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">原来，墓穴中央的魔像是用来抵御入侵者的工具。它们突然惊醒，从柱基上跃了下来，准备杀死任何胆敢踏入这片区域的人。我们的工程师利用从魔像熔炉中学到的东西，成功拆除了魔像的机动促动器，使它们在地上无助地挪动。既然已经解决了魔像的问题，我们现在可以接近至尊领主了。</Data></Cell></Row><Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0"><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TYRES_TOMB</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PHASE_4_CHOICE_2_CONTINUE_COMBAT</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The corrupted High Lord lingers here still, guarding at the tomb's heart.</Data></Cell><Cell><Data ss:Type="String">堕落的至尊领主仍然在这里徘徊，守护着坟墓的中心。</Data></Cell></Row></Table><WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"><Unsynced/><Print><ValidPrinterInfo/><HorizontalResolution>600</HorizontalResolution><VerticalResolution>600</VerticalResolution></Print><Selected/><TopRowVisible>182</TopRowVisible><Panes><Pane><Number>3</Number><ActiveRow>223</ActiveRow><ActiveCol>2</ActiveCol></Pane></Panes><ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects><ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios></WorksheetOptions></Worksheet></Workbook>